Everyone is destined by Christ to rise.
I have cried oh walking with God.
[music] Let me tell you the truth. If
anybody tells you walking with God is
just full of laughter, you are joking.
It's not the God of the Bible. Every
generation will not be confused. There
is a generation that will get this thing
from that day. The creative dimension
[music] of the prophetic.
You know, I almost immediately I felt at
peace. I felt at home. Then the next
thing was he welcomed me to join him on
the table to eat. And I was like, I came
for a solution here and not to eat. But
you know, I just couldn't believe that a
man at his level could invite me to come
and join him. Almost immediately, you
know, this sense of inferiority complex
died like almost immediately. outside
the pit. If you are privileged to stay
with Apostle or stay around him, you
will see that Apostle is a love
personified. If it's possible you are
you are you you are with him, you will
want to pause the hand of clock because
he will not want the time to go spending
time with him. You will see his love.
You will see his heart. You will see his
passion. You he can use everything to
teach you at any time.
>> Not only
I thank you. May God bless you and and
God will always be with you in all your
situations. I want to say a very big
thank you daddy for everything. No one
have ever drifted me such like this but
I want to say a very big thank you
>> Apostle Joshua Ascend man. I want to
thank you so much for this great gift.
May God bless you. This will never be
the last birthday you will celebrate in
Jesus name. Amen.
>> And in many ways that became the story
of the entire [screaming]
>> as the program came to an end.
>> The vice [music] principal summed up the
day worldwide for coming to our school.
We pray the good Lord will bless and
replenish you and give YOU GRACE AS you
walk in God's vineard. Thank you for
coming. We appreciate you. Thank you.
[music]
From Paladin, [music]
the journey continues to this time the
streets are on [music] the street.
Members of the community work force
moved through the community [music] with
music.
[music]
A beautiful 9 a.m. [music]
is visiting this territory and Jesus
[music] is being revealed and glorified.
[music]
>> What seemed like a simple rally became
an invitation.
[music]
>> By the end of the day, anticipation for
the community. Habusa [music]
was ready.
>> [music]
[cheering]
>> Long before the crusade began, another
team was ready at work. Medical and
dental professionals arrived early,
preparing to serve residents through
preconultation,
treatment, and medication.
principalities, OVER EVERY DISEASES,
OVER EVERY demonic forces.
>> One to 11 people came, young and old,
parents and children, friends and
neighbors.
>> Scripture would always say, "For God so
loved the world that he gave his only
begotten son." Now, this is the life of
Apostle Joshua Salman made flesh.
Really, because in his love for people,
you find him giving. And this is one of
the things that we want to model today.
We are here giving back to the people of
Kabusa by giving them free medical
attention, free drugs, making sure that
they are healthy and giving them all of
these items for free.
>> After the patient have seen the doctor
and the doctor requests for a test, this
is where they come for the test.
Depending on the request in their form
when we carry out the test, we send them
back to the doctor or to the pharmacy.
While preparations continued, another
need became impossible to ignore. The
road leading into the community had
deteriorated badly over time.
Right.
The crusade ground filled with people.
Worship filled the air. Prayers were
lifted and the gospel was preached.
For many in attendance, it felt personal
as though God was speaking directly into
situations they had carried for years,
for your healing,
but also FOR YOUR DELIVERANCE.
THERE are people who came here tonight.
You are ready TO RECEIVE JESUS,
BUT YOU also want to be delivered.
You want THE CHAINS OF CAPTIVITY BROKEN.
It becomes an error
for you TO COME UNDER THIS ATMOSPHERE
and not have an expectation.
Man of God, there's a miracle here.
>> My goodness.
>> This lady came to the crusade. She had
an issue with her spinal cord. She said
she could not run before. SHE COULD NOT
RUN, BUT NOW SHE CAN RUN.
>> GO AHEAD AND RUN.
>> Show the devil that Jesus.
>> Lives were touched. Hearts were healed.
Many surrendered their lives to Christ.
Others found peace, hope, and renewed
faith.
And as the night came to an end, relief
materials and food items were
distributed to families across the
community
>> because compassion is most powerful when
it is both spoken and demonstrated.
Thank you Apostle Joshua Selman for
visiting our community. Thank you for
the community service, the health care
service and the healing and the miracle
crusade. Thank you for the spiritual
food. Happy birthday to man of God. We
appreciate for the gift given onto us
and we pray that God will furnish his
pocket in the mighty name of Jesus.
>> But project honor did not end in Kabuza.
The Manchester and London members of the
Coonia family joined in expressing the
same values. We are in the city of
London to celebrate our dear apostles
birthday.
>> As Coonia, one of our key things is to
go out into the community and impact
families. We're here in the heart of
London in the Hellrop Community Center
and today we're going to be touching our
families. [music]
Apostle has taught us that the gospel
[music] must be translated to a context
that blesses people but also transforms
society and that's what we wanted to to
do today replicate that which Jesus
Christ did sharing our love with the
community revealing Jesus through the
little things through the big things to
your church
and it really means a lot to them. Thank
you very much for what you brought and
what you donated also for our community
and uh the good uh the good atmosphere
you brought to yourself.
>> Hello everyone. [music]
We are here in the city of Manchester
celebrate our dear father's birthday.
[music] We are sharing the gospel to the
community and resources as well. [music]
The impact we're having on the community
helps the young the old children. are
giving out [music] silent honor our
father
[music]
>> Daria where the ministry first began
different [music] locations different
communities the same heart it was a
reminder that what is consistently
modeled does not stay in one place, it
travels, it grows and it continues to
touch lives wherever it goes.
Among all the initiatives carried out
during project honor, one stood as a
lasting symbol of practical love. At the
University of Abuja, students had
[music] struggled for years with
inconsistent access to water in their
host.
What many considered a basic necessity
had become a daily challenge. As part of
project honor, bho and modern water
facilities were installed for both the
male and the female host is to fulfill a
desire to honor a man whose life and
ministry
has impacted us greatly.
A man who has demonstrated consistently
that genuine Christianity
must be translated in a context that
benefits society. During the
commissioning, Lady Sandra addressed the
gathering and spoke about the importance
of practical obedience
>> and that if they have in any way not
been doing very well, especially
academically, we know they are excellent
students in the school. We've come to
measure another cubit to the students
that this institute to be recognized for
raising students of notoriety.
>> Amen.
>> In the name of Jesus.
>> Coronia Global.
>> Yes. In honor of Apostle Joshua Salman,
>> yes,
>> permit me to put great Apostle Joshua
Salman
whose life and ministry have inspired
faith and transformed lives across
territories.
>> Also during the commissioning another
need was mentioned, a similar challenge
facing the faculty of education. There
was no demand No expectation, just an
honest expression of need
>> has been in d need of adequate water.
>> My god,
>> there are holes we have sunk. They're
not quite yielding and that is why where
this particular Soviet was picked is a
little far and then that's where we have
the challenge of the terrain and that's
why we're here. and continue to plead
that if you can extend that good gesture
and do the third ones, the university
will be really really great.
>> And in that moment, the spirits behind
project honor became clear once again.
Love does not ask, have we done enough?
It asks who else can we help?
>> I used to suffer inferiority for over 22
years and then I listened to a sermon.
He said his only limitation is the voice
of God and process. It was like fire in
my bones. Then I realized that there was
nothing impossible for me to do.
One of my favorite quotes from daddy is
that if there are four foolish people
around you, you did not count well. you
are the fifth and for me that means I
cannot be foolish. So because of that I
decide to make sure I keep coming and
most especially connecting to where I
came from from the other religion and
how coming to Kona have shown me the
difference between where I used to be
and where I am now.
>> Listening to the messages it affects
your life in every area in your marriage
in your finances in your health every
area of your life. It
>> has helped me to love myself. It has
helped me to love every other person
around me honestly and it has just been
a very beautiful journey just having a
relationship with God because it helps
you to understand what you're to do for
him. So your assignment, your purpose
and just gives life's meaning. Apostle
Joshua Salman has taught us to
prioritize the transformation of our
minds through which we produce results
that in turn brings glory to God. It is
such an honor, truly an honor to be both
fathered and mentored by an amazing king
priest. We call him the wise master
builder, Apostle Joshua Sman. Thank you
for saying yes to Jesus in your yes. We
all found our yes or our yeses. We honor
you eternally. Eternally, sir, we are
honored. Thank you, sir. Happy birthday.
[screaming]
>> [cheering]
>> If you are still sitting, I'm suspecting
you. Come on. Come on. Come on.
If you are still sitting, I'm suspecting
you. Is that the best you can do for
Jesus?
I think worship team. Is that the best
you can do for Jesus? Come on. LET
HEAVEN HEAR YOUR VOICE. [music]
COME ON. COME ON. LET'S SEND THE DEVIL
BACK TO HER WITH OUR SHOUT. Give the
Lord a big BIG BIG MAKE IT LOUDER. MAKE
IT LOUDER. MAKE IT LOUDER.
[music]
HALLELUJAH. Before you take your seat,
Daddy Conia Global, we say thank you.
Thank you. Thank you, sir. Thank you for
being a father, a mentor. Thank you for
loving us, for pouring out yourself to
us. We are grateful. We worship God, but
we honor men. Thank you, sir. Please,
can you celebrate God one more time?
Bless you. We [music] bless you. We
bless you. Give him thanks. Wave your
hands from side to side to mean thank
you, Jesus. Wave your hands from side to
side to mean I [music] am grateful
Jesus.
Wave your hands from side to side to
mean I am expectant [music] tonight.
Thank you Jesus for your wonder walking
power. Thank you for wisdom. Thank you
for your love. We bless you. [music] We
bless you. A grateful person is saying
thank you. A thoughtful person is saying
thank you. A wise person is saying thank
you.
[music]
Blessed be the name of the Lord.
Father I'm here tonight. Give me a
visitation. Give me an encounter. Lift
your hands. Lift your voices and pray
passionately. I am here tonight. [music]
You have not called the seed of Jacob to
seek you in vain. I am here tonight.
Give me an encounter. [music]
Give me a visitation.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Thank you. Thank you Jesus.
Hallelujah.
Praise the name of the Lord.
I want us to pray just one prayer.
Whilst they were singing, it just fired
into my spirit again.
You're going to pray and this prayer is
not asking God. You are making a
declaration that in the name of Jesus, I
can never fail
in the name of Jesus. It's a choice that
I have made. I reject it consciously. I
decree and declare that I'm victorious
in Christ. Lift your voice and pray.
Everyone, no distraction. You are
praying.
Regardless what situation you are in
right now, you are declaring as an act
of faith intentionally.
Come on, someone declare I cannot fail.
Victory is on my side. I cannot fail.
The faithful one is by my side. I cannot
fail. Wisdom is by my side. I cannot
fail. Favor is by my side. Ah, I cannot
[music] fail. Power is by my side.
I shake away from the shackles of defeat
consciousness. [music] I decree I cannot
fail. Make sure you are praying.
[music] I am victorious.
Victorious.
I'm a winner.
I'm an expression of divine
possibilities.
prosperous, blessed, favored, highly
favored, anointed. Come on believers,
open your mouth and prophesy.
Open your mouth and participate
in the manifestation of possibilities in
your life. [music]
I cannot fail in the name of Jesus.
Indomitable,
invincible,
lifted above failure by mercy. Lifted
above failure by the word.
[music]
Make sure you are praying.
In Jesus mighty name we pray. [music]
My Bible says, "Let the redeemed of the
Lord say so." Say so. Say so. This mouth
you have is not just for complaining.
It is a miraculous tool you use to
participate as far as your destiny is
concerned. If you shut your mouth, you
shut your destiny
in the name of Jesus. I welcome you on
behalf of Jesus, the son of the living
God, to our sixth miracle service for
this year.
Hallelujah.
Miracle service for the month of June.
The Lord is determined
like never before to see to it that you
experience the fullness of a life of
dominion, victory, breakthrough,
healing, and every other thing your
faith puts in the name of Jesus. It's up
to your faith to fill in the blank. For
someone, it can be promotion, elevation,
direction, whatever it is that your
faith can put fill in the blank. But I
pray for you [music]
in the name of Jesus that by the time
you are sharing the grace, you will be
carrying a truckload of blessings.
You believe that? Say amen.
You believe that? Say amen again.
Hallelujah.
Lord Jesus, we look to you tonight
as vessels, as sons, as daughters, as
children, as a maid looks onto her
mistress for mercy and for [music] help.
And we thank you because we are aware
that you are not just a good God, you
are a merciful God. You are a powerful
God. And you are a loving father. And so
we approach you with this assurance
tonight that we will not go back the way
we came.
>> Your word declares that you have not
called the seed of Jacob to seek you in
vain. We have come as proof that we
believe you. We have come as proof that
we love you. We have come with our
hearts open to receive not just of your
word but the blessings [music] that are
assured in your word. Therefore, Lord,
we pray that you will visit us in a very
mighty way,
>> very mighty way. Grant unto everyone the
desires of our heart.
>> And we decree and declare by the power
of the Holy Spirit that you will be
glorified.
>> Be glorified.
[music]
Be [singing]
glorified.
That's [music] our prayer. Lord, we
[singing]
glorify
be [music]
>> like a mighty orchestra. Can we lift up
our voices in worship be
glorified [music]
be
glorified. [singing]
>> Now sing be magnified. [music]
Be
magnified.
Be [music]
>> What a beautiful sound in his ears. Sing
magi.
[music]
Be
magnified.
>> Sing. Be glorified in the heavens.
[music]
Be glorified
in the heaven.
>> Be glorified in the earth.
>> Be glorified [music]
in the earth.
>> And be glorified in this temple. Be
glorified [music]
in this temple.
>> Jesus.
Jesus. [music]
Jesus.
[music]
Be glorified in the heavens. Everyone
>> be glorified [music]
in the heaven.
[music] Be glorified [singing] in the
earth. [music]
Be glorified
in this temple.
[music] Jesus.
Jesus.
adore. [music]
>> You are Jesus. [singing]
[music]
>> Jesus
[music] be the glory.
[music]
You are [singing] saveior.
You're [music] my savior.
[music]
My savior. [singing]
The [music] one you say
has come to worship you. [music]
The one you say.
>> [music]
>> Lift your voice and sing him to be your
healer tonight.
[music]
>> He sent forth his word and his word heal
them. [music]
[music] You're my healer, Lord.
>> [music]
>> The one you hear
has [music] come to worship you.
The one you go.
>> How many of you have received [music]
help from the Lord? Can we cry out to
the helper tonight?
[music]
The stone of hell. knees [music] all
down.
[music]
You are my helper.
No one
[music]
with your hands
that mean he's your helper. Everybody
with your hands lift up to heaven.
[music]
You are the help.
>> You are the helper.
[music]
>> [music]
>> I come to worship you. The one you
[music] come to worship to worship you.
The one you [music] held. The one you
held
has come to worship [music]
you.
The one you held
has [music] come to worship you.
>> The one you blessed.
>> The one you blessed
>> has come to worship you.
The one you blessed.
I have searched and searched
all the earth. I have searched and
searched [music]
all the earth and I found them by the
way. [music]
>> That's my conclusion. I have searched
and searched all [music] the earth.
searched and searched all the earth have
found.
[music]
Just sing one time to the king, [music]
to the maker, the creator, the great
one. I'm come
[music]
out
of town.
No one [music] like you across the
earth.
I'm a [singing] come.
>> [music]
>> in a [music] class all by yourself. The
mighty God, the King, the Father, the
righteous judge.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Father, we worship you like this because
there is no other way to do it. There's
no other way to let the nations know
that you are faithful. You are mighty,
dependable, reliable,
incontestable in a class all by
yourself.
If we write, we are still limited. If we
preach, we are still limited. Even when
we sing, [music] we are still limited.
But let this be a token of our
gratitude, an expression of deep honor,
deep honor to you. Our father, our
maker, our king, and our judge. Let the
nations know that we worship the one
true God [music] and Jesus, your son.
[music] be glorified tonight.
Be glorified tonight.
In Jesus name we pray.
[music] Please, you may be seated if
you're able to. When we take the time to
worship God,
it's not a waste of time at all. It's a
declaration of his power, his majesty,
and also a declaration of our gratitude,
our gratitude to God. I don't know about
you, but sometimes I get overwhelmed
just thinking of his faithfulness, his
mercy in my life and over this great
house. And um I can only say thank you
Jesus. Would you join me? Say again,
thank you Jesus.
>> Thank you Jesus.
>> Hallelujah. And now let me repeat for
probably one last time. Thank you to
Coonia Global, to the body of Christ, to
the workforce, and to everyone for
making this week a memorable and
heartfelt one for me sitting quietly and
just watching the projects that were
executed. This what you saw um is just
about half of the various projects that
were done across, you know, even
non-coonia platforms. There were people
who just went out of their way from
intercession to welfare
and all kinds of things. The beauty of
leadership
is that your investment of time, energy
and knowledge in people um that you are
able to watch in your lifetime as people
evolve, as people grow. And you cannot
imagine how
rewarding it is for me to watch
supposedly ordinary people doing great
things for the kingdom. The Christian
faith, if communicated properly, does
not raise fanatics.
It will raise passionate, well-rounded
believers.
I am a strong advocate of translating
the reality of the spirit life to a
context that reveals Jesus across the
cosmos.
It can start in your secret place. It
can start from and through the health of
your altar but it cannot end there. If
it ends there, your Christian experience
is not efficient. The value of witness
is that it starts from the secret place
and then it ends in society. You can
imagine the lives that have been
blessed. Children who have seen these
ones who came to bless them as models is
given them a reason, a graphic, a
personified reason to say yes to Jesus
and to live for him. This right there is
what we call kingdom come. Beyond
falling and rising, beyond jumping and
shouting, now you give an intelligent
person a reason to see that your
impartations and the encounter in church
is not wasting away precious destinies.
You can import the reality of the spirit
life, the kingdom life, and then you
leave this place equipped to represent
Christ in a way that is undeniable, in a
way that will cause a praise to spring
out from the hearts of supposedly
ordinary people, Christians and
non-Christians alike, and they attest to
the fact that you have met God. And for
all those who have involved in these
projects whether known or not known
whether documented or not documented may
my God bless you
>> in the name of Jesus. You have swn the
seed of honor indeed you will reap a
harvest of honor
>> in Jesus marvelous name we pray. Amen.
Tonight again is miracle service and the
Lord quickened in my heart to take the
time tonight to really pray for the sick
and so I'll just set the pace and then
we'll have the time to pray and see how
far God will help us. There are people
whose bodies need miracles. There are
people who we have been sent to tonight
and we're trusting that Rafa will reveal
himself in a mighty way. that people who
have come with burdens especially all
kinds of bodily infirmities if you study
the ministry of Jesus every time the
gospel was communicated it went handin
glove with the healing ministry you
cannot separate the communication of the
gospel or the revelation of the life of
Jesus and not include the ministry of
healing now healing was not the only
thing Jesus did there were deliverances
there were breakthroughs there were
multiplications but if there was One out
of the many things that he did that was
consistent with the preaching of the
gospel is the healing. Because what
salvation does to the spirit of man is
what healing does to the body.
Hallelujah. And while the more excellent
way is to walk in health and vitality,
there are times where you will have to
deal with emergencies, all kinds of
satanic illnesses that plague God's
people. You find people smiling but you
have no idea the things they are
battling with. And it's not everyone who
is a victim of irresponsibility.
There are people who have made concerted
efforts but is very clear that their
situations their bodily um you know
challenges are a direct attack from the
kingdom of darkness.
But let me say this
and at the risk of sounding proud I want
you to listen to me. I know today's
miracle service but if you pay attention
to the things that you are learning
if you submit truly nonp pretentiously
dedicatedly to the things that you are
learning line upon line I give you a
guarantee by the integrity of God's word
as captured in this book that I lived
before you if you will pay attention the
assignment of priesthood is not just to
intercede for you but to be able to
serve you the word of God distilled
through years of study
through the mercy of God and it's
[music] tailor made for your rising
everything God prepares in this service
is not for himself is for you he feelth
all things and in all God does not need
promotion listen please God does not
need healing God does not need an
anointing God does not need impartation.
God does not need a job. God does not
need a wife or a husband. Are we
together?
Yeah.
God does not need increase. God does not
need a political position. God is not
hungry to seek bread from you. Not
thirsty to seek water or wine from you.
He's God. That's why he's called God.
But you need everything I've mentioned
right now and more. and he's made the
way available. God's method will always
be his word. Always be his word. And
there are different layers of the word
of God. There are at least four layers
of the word of God. I'm not that's
that's not my discussion tonight. But
there is what we call the written word.
There is what we call the spoken word.
There is what we call the revealed word.
There is what we call the sent word. The
Bible captures all of these dimensions.
They don't achieve the same thing.
Hallelujah. The written word, the Bible
says, "Ye search the scripture for an
example." You see that now? And you will
think in them, you will find, but they
are they which testify of me. The Bible
says, "The things that are written are
for time. They are written for our
learning. So that we through the comfort
of the scripture that is written, we
might find hope." There is the spoken
word. Hallelujah. Yes.
the spoken word.
There is the revealed word. The Bible
says in John chapter 1 verse1, in the
beginning the word was with God. The
word was God.
But by the time we get to, I think
chapter 14 or so, it says the word
became flesh. Became flesh. The word
became flesh. It was revealed to us. The
Bible says you shall call him Emmanuel
for interpreting that it means God has
been revealed in the midst of his
people.
There is the sent word and we'll be
considering that hopefully in the course
of our charge. He sent forth his word.
His word healed them and delivered them
from all their oppression. I think it's
Isaiah 55 10 and 11. It says, "So shall
my word be that goeth forth from out of
my mouth. It shall not return to me
void, but it shall accomplish what I
pleased and prosper in the thing or the
purpose for which I sent it.
I sent it. [music]
I sent it. Hallelujah.
So, very quickly, let me establish a few
things. When preparing for a service
like this, I always like to shelf any
attempt to be creative and I prefer
yieldedness. I just stay with God and
allow him speak to my heart that which
he would want his people to hear to
learn because his power follows his
voice follows his word. Wherever the
word of God goes, there goes the power
of God. And you don't want to be at the
other side of God's word. If God's word
is going left, you can be sure his power
is going left. And if you find yourself
at the other side, then it will take the
mercy of God to help you. And God has
quickened a very important subject as to
why many believers do not make strategic
progress in their lives. And what I'm
about to give you as a charge is all
encompassing. Whether your desire is
healing,
financial miracles, breakthroughs, or
whatever it is, um what I'm going to
share with you very briefly and then
we'll get to the ministry of the spirit.
I think it will profit you. So let your
heart be opened in Jesus name.
Your life will never advance beyond the
quality of your choices and decisions.
Any and every aspect of your life
remains at the mercy of the quality of
your choices and your decisions.
I wrote here decisions truly decide the
quality of your life.
God has already made it very clear that
he desires the best at least two
scriptures. One, I am come that ye may
have life and that you have that life
more abundantly. Amplified says to its
fullest. John chapter 10 and verse 10.
The B part he desired this. The Bible
says, "He that did not spare his son,
but he gave him up for us. How much more
with him shall he give us all things
freely to enjoy." It says, "I wish above
all things that he may prosper and be in
health, even as your soul prospers." God
desires this for us. Jeremiah 29:11, "I
know the thoughts that I think towards
you, sayeth the Lord, they are thoughts
of peace and not of evil, to bring you a
future and a hope or an expected end.
You do not suddenly arrive at a great
destiny. You decide your way there. You
do not suddenly arrive at a great
destiny." There are many sincere
believers whose orientation is that one
day because they are in Christ. One day
because perhaps they are born again.
They believe and they are convinced
sometimes even beyond change that a
glorious destiny will suddenly happen to
them one day in the buy and buy. You do
not suddenly arrive at a great destiny.
You decide your way there.
God desires your good. I wrote here, but
your decisions can reject his offer. God
desires your good, but your decisions
can reject his offer. God's offer at any
level for you and I is never by force.
God has proposed great and mighty
things. The Bible calls them exceeding
great and precious promises that by them
we might be partakers of his divine
nature, having escaped the corruption
that is in the world through lust.
However, your decisions or perhaps your
indecisions can reject his offer. Are we
learning already? In a similar vein,
Satan desires you evil. He desires your
destruction. The Bible says the thief
cometh not but for to kill, to steal,
and to destroy. Satan desires you evil,
but your decisions can reject his plans.
Please listen very carefully that God
desires your good.
He desires the best for your life, for
your family, for your business, for your
work, for your church, for your destiny.
Settle that for a fact. Regardless what
you are going through right now, let God
be true. and all men and even all
conditions be liars. Never allow what is
happening around you to shift you from
this orientation. God is a good God. The
Bible says every good and every perfect
thing comes down from above from the
father of light in whom there is no
shadow of turning or variableness.
As far as his desire concerning you is
concerned, God will not change his mind.
He desires your good. But your
decisions, your choices can reject his
offer and he will respect it. Satan
desires your evil, meaning your
destruction, desires everything bad in
your life or to happen to your life. But
your decisions can reject his plans.
This is good news.
Your decisions, I wrote here, or
indecisions have led you to where you
are today. This is a very uncomfortable
truth that your decisions aggregated
through the years or your indecisions
have contributed largely to where you
are today.
Your decisions also have the power to
lead you from where you are now. Listen,
your decisions did not only bring you
this far. Still within the power to
choose is the power to lead you to the
place of destiny or to the place of
further decline. So it doesn't matter
what where you are in destiny right now
as it stands. Whether it's good or bad,
whether it's a place of blessing or a
place of defeat, we are saying that your
decision still contains the power to
move you from where you are today, right
now, to the place of destiny
or to move you to the place of further
decline.
Decisions are the bridge between your
current reality and your desired or
prophetic destiny. decisions are the
bridge between your current reality
and your desired or prophetic destiny.
Apostle, for me, I'm trusting God that I
will in no time become a great man of
God impacting the nations for Jesus.
That desired or that prophetic destiny
you just proposed is at the mercy of
your decisions.
Apostle, I desire to take my family to a
more responsible position where I'm able
to meet their needs without worry. From
where you are right now, to the place
you need to be by desire or
prophetically, it'll take the quality of
your decisions. Apostle, for me, I'm in
a pit right now. My aunt's head has gone
down. I don't even know where to go. I
don't know how to start. right where you
are. It's going to take a decision to
bring you out of that situation and into
a place that glorifies God. Now listen
carefully.
I wrote here and it's a long read but
just listen. I thought um to just read
it the way it came to my spirit. Many
people pray for things that only quality
decisions and choices can solve. Many
many people pray for things that quality
decisions and choices can solve. Now as
all important as prayer is, as all
important as fasting is, as all
important as church attendance is, it is
not a substitute for the responsibility
of making quality choices.
As all important as prayer is, as all
important as fasting is, as all
important as church attendance is,
faithfulness as far as coming to the
house of God is concerned, none of them
can become a substitute for taking the
responsibility of making quality
decisions and choices. They in fact act
as the basis to empower you so that you
are able to eventually make quality
decisions.
Is someone learning? If you're learning,
say amen.
>> Amen.
>> Now listen, you cannot pray your way
alone out of a life of indisipline. For
an example, if what is plaguing you is
in discipline, you cannot use prayer
alone to pray your way out of a life of
inisipline. Now you start by praying to
obtain the enabling grace. But
eventually you will have to take
advantage of that grace and use your
will to make a decision that from today
there will be a shift in my character, a
shift in my life.
Hallelujah.
You cannot pray and fast your way alone
into for an example sustainable
financial abundance. It's wonderful to
pray. There is a place for it. It's
wonderful to fast. But you cannot pray
your way alone into sustainable
financial abundance. If you have not
decided to learn the principles of say
value, management and increase.
Just these three principles for an
instance. No matter how hard you pray,
no matter how hard you fast, it may
attract instant breakthrough but you are
not going to have sustainability with
respect to say for an example your
finances. In addition to that prayer, it
should supply the wisdom and the grace
so that you explore the principles of
say value of management of increase.
You see the reason why it looks like the
prayer of many believers even though we
invest energy, we invest time and we
invest consistency. The reason why our
prayer life seems to mock the ability of
God is because we do not know that there
is a responsibility component to
effective living. Are we together? So in
the place of prayer when we say Lord I
give it all to you. You are talking of
your life. Even when you say I lay down
my will. Are we together? What you are
saying is that I align to what you want.
When I know what you want, I make
choices and decisions that are
consistent with what you want.
What does it mean to choose? What does
it mean to decide?
To choose means to conclude on a path to
follow after a careful examination of
the various outcomes and consequences
they produce. Let me take that slowly.
Let me take that slowly. This I need you
to write. To choose means to conclude on
a path to follow
after a careful examination of the
various outcomes and the consequences
they produce. For one last time, to
choose means to conclude on a path to
follow after a careful examination of
the various outcomes and the
consequences they produce.
What then does it mean to decide? There
are similar words that we play around
with, but they are not exactly the same.
To decide, on the other hand, means to
be willing to back your choices or
conclusions with consistent action.
Let me take that again. To decide means
to be willing to back your choices and
your conclusions with consistent action.
So while choice has to deal with
selecting the wisest option, a decision
is acting on the choices so that they
deliver.
It takes choices and decisions together
to bring acceleration and to move you
forward. If you care, let me recap one
last time. To choose means to conclude
on a path to follow after a careful
examination of the various outcomes and
consequences. Take note of that word
that they produce.
To decide on the other hand means to be
willing to back your choices or your
conclusions with consistent action.
Generally speaking, choices and
decisions are pathways.
All choices, all decisions lead you
somewhere, whether good or bad.
All choices.
The decision to love Jesus leads you
somewhere. The decision to be unserious
spiritually leads you somewhere. The
decision to be responsible leads you
somewhere. The decision to be
irresponsible lead you somewhere. Am I
right on that? The decision to show
honor leads you somewhere. Produces a
certain kind of outcome. The decision to
be arrogant and lawless leads you
somewhere. The decision to love leads
you somewhere. The decision to hate
leads you somewhere. The decision to be
prayerful as a lifestyle produces a
certain texture of a believer in your
life. The decision to be lukewarm
spiritually
produces something too in your life.
There is no decision and no choice that
leaves you the same way. Like you may
have learned, you only have the power to
choose and decide. What you choose and
decide already has consequences
connected to them. You don't choose
consequences. The consequences are
automatic.
Is someone learning now? You only have
the liberty to make the choices and the
decisions and then the consequences
follow. Consequence simply talks about a
correspondent outcome.
If you decide to love God, that is a
choice. That is a decision. When you
actually now begin to love God and there
are consequences that follow that
decision. For an example a vibrant
spiritual life. For an example, favor
with God. for an example, an upgrade in
your capacity spiritually until you
become a person of stature. So when you
find people enjoying
or being punished by their consequences,
it is seldom the doing of God. Are we
together now? God has made his
proposition clear as far as the Bible is
concerned. Look up please. How many of
you know it is not only God that has a
proposal for you? Satan has a proposal.
Life has a proposal. He said, "I set
before you this day life and death,
blessing and cursing. I can only advise
you. I can't I can't force you to choose
life. But be aware while choosing that
the implication will go beyond you. It
will affect you and your seed, you and
your business, you and your ministry,
you and your finances, you and your
company."
Is someone learning? Many believers
pray. Many believers fast. Many
believers come to church. But not many
people have really taken the time to
study the implication of indecision or a
poor decision as far as actualizing
their destinies are concerned.
Hallelujah.
It takes making decisions to rise in
life or to fail in life. When you find
someone perpetually rising, it's not
just the grace of God. It is the grace
of God maximized.
The grace of God maximized by making
quality decisions. When you find someone
painfully failing in life consistently,
it is the grace of God ignored through
the level the kinds of decisions that we
make.
Maybe I should recap on a statement that
I made one time when teaching on
choices. I just found it very useful to
include it here. The major way curses,
enchantments, and demonic activities
work. The major way curses,
work is to manipulate you into making
wrong choices and decisions. It is one
of the major way that curses or
enchantments work. They don't just work
automatically and veto your will and
bring you into derision or bring you
into a life of failure. What they do is
to alter your capacity to make proestiny
choices. And while you are concentrating
on blaming Satan, you're unaware of how
much you are participating in making his
proposal manifest in your life. Is
someone learning now?
The real value of wisdom
is in its ability to help or empower you
to make superior
destiny advancing choices and decisions.
The real value of wisdom is not just so
you say I am wise. The real value of
wisdom is not just to say you are
knowledgeable. The real value of wisdom
is in its ability to empower your
destiny your your choices so that you
make superior destiny advancing choices.
For an example you had a choice to be
anywhere else in this city in this
nation or around the world by this time.
Those who are following from across the
globe right now whilst listening some of
you have been listening from the start
of the service you have the option of
shutting down and going to do something
else with your life but you have chosen
as proof that wisdom resides in you. You
have seen the value that investing an
hour or two or three will change your
life versus doing something else may not
be bad but you just place value on the
word of God the anointing and the
ministry of the Holy Spirit.
Don't tell me you are wise. Let me see
the quality of your decisions. If your
decisions quantum leap you from where
you are closer to the place of destiny
then I know that the wisdom of God is at
work in you. And you don't need to tell
me you are foolish. YOU JUST DECIDE and
let me watch you because your decision
is a conclusion. You have weighed many
parameters. Are we together now?
Decisions decide destiny.
praying,
fasting, faithful church attendance,
spiritual activities without the
willingness to make choices and
decisions will still leave the believer
frustrated. It's a sad reality, but it
is true that in addition, now please
don't get me wrong, I'm only contrasting
these spiritual activities with respect
to my emphasis tonight. Never
downplaying any of them. I'm just
telling you that they were not supposed
to be a replacement to this allimp
important aspect of our lives.
Praying, fasting, church attendance and
any other kind of spiritual activity
without the willingness to make choices
and decisions will still leave the
believer frustrated.
While meditating on this, the picture
that came to me is driving a vehicle.
Please look at me. When you are driving
a vehicle to move you from where you are
to where you need to be, there are many
things that are involved in making that
vehicle move. At the very least, there
is an ignition, right? You you you put
on your ignition and then you engage
your gear system and then you begin to
press your accelerator. Now look at
this. I consider the ignition and
engaging the gear system like the other
spiritual activities, praying, fasting,
attending church, but making choices to
me is like the brake and the
accelerator. How many of you have seen
that even though you engage the gear
system in your car, you hold onto the
wheels, if you do not press the
accelerator, the car will not move.
THERE ARE TIMES THAT ALL IS SET BUT
PERHAPS MAYBE YOU are talking with
someone about to move and then you are
not able to move for a long time. It's
not because the vehicle is not on. It's
not because the gear system is not
engaged is because you did not press the
accelerator. The accelerator is what
controls speed. The brake is what
regulates the speed. These two represent
for me the power to choose, the power to
decide. So there are many believers in
the PLACE OF PRAYER. THERE'S FIRE IN
YOUR VEHICLE. THE IGNITION is on.
You have learned through wisdom to know
that oh there's gear 1, 2, 3, there's
reverse, there's neutral, there's park.
You know that much and YOU HAVE EVEN
ENGAGED the gear. It's ready TO DRIVE.
YOU'VE HELD ON TO the wheels. But you
are not making anything. You are just
saying, "Lord, I believe this car will
take me to the place of destiny." And
God is saying the ignition is not the
only thing need for your needed for your
movement, the accelerator and the brake.
You've not attended to it.
And for many people, they've been there
holding on to the wheels. I pray for you
in the name of Jesus, you will complete
that process tonight that moves your
vehicle.
>> Shout a believing amen to the place of
destiny.
Now the flip side is that how many of
you know that matching the accelerator
and the bra and the brake is useless
when the car is not on. Am I am I right
on that? Is useless when the gear system
is not engaged. That's an example of
what the Bible says. It is vain to wake
up early in the morning and to sleep
late at night. There are people who
match the throttle and the brake
together. They want the car to move. But
the problem is that the manufacturer
designed the value of that brake and
that accelerator to only work for you
when the ignition is on and when the
brake system uh when the the uh um the
gear system is engaged. Are we together
now? So if you ignore God, ignore every
other thing and you keep doing the
mechanics, you will find out that it
will not work.
Is someone learning?
Many many believers desire to move
forward. They truly do. But most of them
do not know that this miracle God gave
man called the will. W I l it's a
miracle.
Master, if you want to, you are able to
heal us. And Jesus said, I will be thou
cleansed. The will of man is powerful.
Powerful. No matter what you lose in
life, in my opinion, the worst case of a
human being is not really the one who's
lost his eyes or ability to walk. The
one who's lost the ability to use his
will is the worst human being on earth.
That's the reason why there's no record
of madness that Jesus saw in the Bible
that he did not do anything about. There
were times he saw some cases the Bible
would say he healed them and sometimes
but he took the issue of madness. You
know why? Because it's a hijacking of
your ability to make decisions. The
madman in gatherer
for an example. You see that now?
ANYTHING THAT HIJACKS YOUR ABILITY TO
choose either through manipulation. Are
we together? Whatever it is has truly
destroyed you. A man without a pair of
functional eyes can still maximize life.
Am I are we right on that? There are
people without hands, without limbs,
they are able to maximize life. There
are people with sadly a few organs taken
out of their body. But once they still
have the capacity to be coherent, the
capacity to make intelligent choices.
Some of those people as limited as they
look, they have been able to build
conglomerates. Some of them are leaders,
sound communicators.
One time there was a scientist who lost
almost everything. I don't know the name
of the medical condition, but a machine
was, you know, put together to be able
to help interpret his thoughts. He lost
the ability to move his hands and every
part of his body. But the one thing that
was still left was his coherence, his
ability to be able to express his will.
Madness is a terrible thing. When you
find a madman walking on the street, you
see the things that they do. It looks
like they are aware. They are laughing.
They are crying. They are moving. It's
cold, but they are moving. They are
naked. They don't care. They are dirty.
They are sick. They don't care. That
right there is what you do to your
destiny. When you do not walk in
partnership with God and hold on to the
wheels of your destiny, you take
advantage of God's grace and make
choices and decisions. I'm telling you,
hating where you are does not mean you
have chosen to come out of there. Did
you hear what I said? HATING WHERE YOU
ARE DOES NOT mean you have chosen. I
HATE POVERTY. NO, THAT'S NOT THE CHOICE
to be blessed.
I HATE SATAN. THAT'S NOT THE CHOICE to
be liberated or to walk in liberty. Many
of us think because you have verbalized
your hatred for your current condition,
your hatred and your disdain for where
you are, we automatically think by
verbalizing your hatred, WE HAVE CHOSEN.
NO, IT doesn't work that way. The fact
that you hate Satan does not mean you
love Jesus. No. No.
The fact that you hate poverty does not
mean you have chosen economic
emancipation. The fact that you hate
irresponsibility
does not mean you have chosen a life of
discipline and dignity.
Someone say I choose Jesus. Say I choose
victory. Say that like you are learning.
Say I choose Jesus. I choose victory. I
choose liberty. I [clears throat] choose
excellence. I choose greatness. Yes sir.
He said from where thou art. speaking to
Abraham. I like that scripture. It
inspires me a lot. Not where you want to
go. You may not be able to see where you
want to go, but from where thou art. It
says, "Lift up your eyes and look round
about to the left, northwards,
southwards, eastwards, westwards. From
where you are, from where you are." But
that happened after Lord separated
himself from him. He said, "Now lift up
your eyes from where you are and look
look.
I watch many sincere believers. If you
ask them, do you like the way I give you
an example? I give you an example.
How many of you know that for a miracle
service like this, as much as we thank
God for the multitudes of people
connected across the globe and those who
are here, you will be surprised, with
all due respect, to know that there are
people who live a walking distance,
literally a walking distance away from
here. They are sick. They are oppressed.
They are aware. They know God is here.
They acknowledge that God is here. They
wave at others when they are coming to
receive and the people just say well I
know one day pray for us. Have you heard
those kinds of things? With all due
respect not to not to mock but I tell
you those people do not know that every
time you treat your destiny like that
you are reinforcing your remaining in
that situation.
Once upon a time there was a man in the
Bible. Let me show you the power of
choices. There was a man in the Bible
who was lame. He was crippled.
obviously did not have the power to move
through the crowd. The Bible says they
filled the whole house and he had
friends. I'm sure the Bible does not
record that, but it's safe to assume
that he told his friends, he said,
"Listen, I want you guys to help me or
at least the friend said, "We are taking
you for a program." And he said, "I
agree. I use my wheel. I can't use my
strength. I don't even have enough
strength, but I place my wheel on the
line. Let's go." And the friends may
have told him, listen, it's going to be
a bumpy road because we're about to tear
off a roof and throw you down. We are
not sure ourselves what will happen.
Imagine that you were crippled, God
forbid, and some persons were taking you
safe to Coonia here and um they said
they are going to tear up this roof and
whilst you are teaching you just see
someone banging the roof, banging the
roof and then they throw you down and
you land the remaining life that you
had.
Are you seeing? In other words, it was
safe to say, "DIE IN HIS PRESENCE THERE,
LET HIM KNOW WHAT to do with you." And
yet the man agreed. And the Bible says
when Jesus SAW THEIR FAITH, NOT THEIR
CARELESSNESS. NOW, I'm not saying to do
stupid things. You get the idea. That
day is not today. That's why God gave us
the Holy Ghost.
Cuz sometimes when you preach like this,
you now empower believers to do
something God has been stopping them to
do.
Hallelujah.
Imagine with me for a moment that that
man just, you know, you just drop him
down and he interrupts Jesus's teaching
and Jesus is saying, "What is going on
here?" And the friends are saying,
"We're sorry. We're not disrespectful
people, but we know that you have the
power. We are not sure what city you'll
be going to next. And don't forget,
there was no internet, no vehicles, no
nothing, no electricity. Now that we
have you here, we don't need to waste
that time.
And the Bible says when Jesus saw their
faith, saw their faith. May he see your
faith tonight
>> that in spite of the fact that all of
the overflows are filled. For some of
you who are outside, he still saw you
standing. He's still seeing you
standing. You have a right to go back
home and say, "Look, there's no space
FOR ME." BUT YOU ARE THIS desperate to
go forward. This desperate to know God.
This desperate to love God. This
desperate to end [laughter] the
calamities that have plagued your
family. Can I tell you there's one thing
I know about God. There is a level of
aggression you give to life. Satan will
let you go. I'm telling you, the Bible
says resist.
Resist does not always mean fight. It
means stand upon the word of God. There
is a level of seriousness that is
invested in your destiny. You must
manifest as a champion.
Right from the days of John the Baptist
and until now, the kingdom suffered
violence and the spiritually violent,
the ones who refuse to take no for an
answer that you found yes in the word of
God for your destiny. And you must
insist until that yes manifest in your
life. If I just describe you, shout
amen.
>> Hallelujah.
Apostle mine. Honestly, if God can just
give me money, I will use it. Well, my
brother, God does not give men money. He
gives men wisdom, the power. He He gives
men the capacity to be valuable. Are we
together? Then he helps them to create
the atmosphere that will draw favor
including financial favor to them.
The man who never says I hate poverty
but is listening to the word of God and
reading and learning learning on value.
That man you see he has already chosen
to be blessed. Are we together now? Yes.
Bible says blessed is the man who does
not stand in the counsel of the wicked.
Standing there is your choosing to
remain there. Are we together? nor um
who walks in the counsel of the wicked,
nor stands in the way of sinners, nor
sits in the seat of the scornful. THESE
ARE VARIOUS WAYS OF CHOOSING TO REMAIN
THERE. It says, "But his delight is in
the law of the Lord, and on that law do
he MEDITATE DAY AND NIGHT, that man for
choosing the law of the Lord, he shall
be, I like this, like a TREE THAT'S
PLANTED BY the rivers. It brings forth
his fruit in season." And the Bible says
whose leaf does not wither and
whatsoever he does business, ministry.
TALK TO ME. WHATSOEVER HE DOES, raising
children, there is such a dimension as
WHATSOEVER HE DOES, NOT SOME THINGS HE
DOES, NOT SOME THINGS HE DOES, NOT THE
SPIRITUAL THINGS HE DOES. YOU CAN DO
WELL IN YOUR SPIRITUAL THINGS AND FAIL
IN YOUR FINANCIAL THINGS. THE BIBLE SAYS
THERE is such a realm where you are
planted that whatsoever he does
prospers.
Ministry prospers, business prosper,
your children prosper, every the works
of your hands prosper. You believe that?
I believe it with all my heart.
WHATSOEVER HE DOES. DON'T TELL ME YOU
ARE DOING WELL SPIRITUALLY. IT'S NOT YET
THE realm of whatsoever. There are still
some things working, but some things ARE
NOT WORKING. THAT'S WHY YOU came here.
You came here to press FOR COMPLETION.
LORD, WHILE THANKING YOU for the ones
working, I insist AND I WILL NOT BE
QUIET. SOMEONE SAY AMEN.
>> AMEN. IS ALSO CHOOSING. IT'S A DECISION.
IS SAYING I AGREE. I RELEASE MY WILL.
LET it be so. LET IT BE SO. SAY AMEN.
I choose.
I choose
that curses will end in my life. NOT
JUST THAT JESUS DIED AND ENDED. NO. NO.
HAVE YOU CHOSEN? HAVE YOU CHOSEN? DON'T
SAY JESUS HAS DONE IT. HAVE YOU CHOSEN
TO APPROPRIATE IT in your life? THE SAME
POWER THAT BROUGHT CURSES to an end. IS
THE SAME POWER THAT PLEADED FOR YOUR
HEALTH AND WHOLENESS. IS THE SAME POWER
THAT PLEADED FOR YOUR excelling in life.
BUT THE QUESTION IS, HAVE YOU CHOSEN? MY
SALVATION DOES NOT TRANSLATE TO YOUR
SALVATION. I can only preach to you and
then the Holy GHOST IS WAITING. AS
POWERFUL AS HE IS, he cannot force the
life of God in you until you verbalize
that with my heart I believe. With my
mouth I confess unto my justification
decisions.
You can decide that from today favor
will follow me. It's not just
verbalizing it. After you make that
choice that means you have come to a
conclusion there is favor there is
PROFITLESS LABOR THERE IS HARDSHIP THERE
IS OPPRESSION. THESE ARE the choices and
by the spirit of wisdom you have now
weighed what is the consequence of
retrogression the consequence of
profitless labor. and you arrive by the
spirit that this CHOICE IS HEALTHIEST
FOR MY LIVING EFFECTIVELY and serving
the purposes of God. Therefore, I
choose.
But it translates TO A DECISION WHEN YOU
NOW take the responsibility of WORKING
IN PARTNERSHIP WITH THE WORD OF GOD to
begin to work in keeping with the
principles that make the consequences
profitable.
Listen, let me tell you. No matter what
I say to you, NO MATTER WHAT PRAYER I
pray over your life, if you have not
chosen and you have not decided, I
cannot help you.
The song says, "I have decided to follow
Jesus." It's a very powerful song. Not
that I HAD THE GOSPEL. I decided
I decided.
Jesus looked at the disciples and said,
"Will you also go?" They said, "To whom
shall we go? [music] You alone has the
word of life. Did you read about Opa and
Rof? Is it not in your Bible? Two women
in the same condition. ALL LOST THEIR
CHILDREN. ALL LOST THEIR HUSBANDS and
their mother-in-law. Naomi, she said,
"Please go and fend for yourselves. I'm
a failure. I could not help you as your
mother-in-law." One found her way
without thinking. She chose and that was
the end of it. We don't know what
happened to her. But another said, "No,
I have THE OPTION TO GO LIKE MY
SISTER-IN-LAW, BUT I HAVE CHOSEN THAT
YOUR GOD WILL be my God. Your people
[music] will be my people." She found
Boaz.
DON'T HATE MY SUCCESS. I CHOSE IT. GOD
GAVE ME THE OPTION. I CHOSE IT. DON'T
HATE MY CHILDREN. I CHOSE IT BY MERCY.
LET ME TELL YOU, THE SAME LORD IS RICH
ONTO ALL. THE SAME LORD IS GOD DID NOT
ISOLATE OTHERS AND GAVE OTHERS A
MALPRACTICE. NO, HE MADE IT OPEN. I SET
BEFORE YOU, MY BROTHERS AND MY SISTERS,
LIFE AND DEATH. I SET BEFORE YOU
BLESSING AND CURSING. I SET BEFORE YOU
THE CAPACITY TO BAIL YOUR FAMILY OUT OR
TO JOIN THEM IN THAT PAIN. I SET before
you the opportunity to be a mighty
prophet or to be a BEGGARLY PERSON. I
SET BEFORE YOU THE ABILITY TO CARRY THE
HEALING ANOINTING AND TAKE IT to the
nations. It is up to YOU TO CHOOSE. SAY
I CHOOSE. SAY I DECIDE. SAY I CHOOSE.
SAY I DECIDE.
LISTEN. THAT IS THE ONE THING SATAN
CANNOT FIGHT.
HE FOUGHT JOB. HE FOUGHT JOB DIRTY. BUT
THE ONE THING HE could not fight IS
JOB'S ABILITY. JOB SAID, "THOUGH HE SLAY
ME, YET BY MY CHOICE I CAN BE ANGRY as
an option, but yet I will trust him."
[music]
It's a gift God gave every man.
That gift only dies when you die. Did
you hear what I SAID? THAT GIFT DOES NOT
DIE WHEN YOU FAIL. THAT GIFT DOES NOT
DIE WHEN YOU ARE PERSECUTED.
THAT GIFT DOES NOT DIE WHEN YOU
BACKSLIDE. THAT GIFT DOES NOT DIE WHEN
they hate you.
DON'T TELL ME I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING.
WHAT YOU MEAN IS I DON'T HAVE THE
OUTCOMES THAT DECISION SHOULD BRING. BUT
YOU HAVE THE POWER TO BRING THEM. The
greatest way to bring things is not to
admire them. Is to decide them into your
life. I decide to BE PRAYERFUL. DON'T
WORRY ABOUT THE GRACE. YOU MAKE THE
CHOICE AND THEN YOUR ADVANTAGE OF BEING
A BELIEVER. THE HOLY GHOST COMES TO BACK
YOU. THE HOLY GHOST COME to empower you.
[music]
WHEN YOU SAY, "I CHOOSE TO BE GREAT,"
YOU MAY NOT KNOW HOW IT IS TO BE GREAT.
JUST MAKE THE CHOICE AND HEAVEN WILL
RELEASE HIS ARSENALS, THE forces of
favor, THE FORCES OF KNOWLEDGE. SAY IT
AGAIN. I CHOOSE.
>> I CHOOSE this day. [music]
I choose Jesus. I CHOOSE GLORY. I CHOOSE
GRACE. I choose power. [music]
I choose.
I choose. Apostle, how about my
background? I choose, sir. I choose.
I don't know what my grandfather chose.
I can't change the fact that I came from
him. But now that it is my turn, come on
now. I choose.
[laughter]
>> [music]
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT NEGOTIATIONS THEY HAD
BEFORE I ARRIVED. BUT NOW THAT I AM
HERE, I USE THIS GOD-GIVEN ABILITY. I
choose grace. I choose glory. I choose
dominion. I choose victory. I CHOOSE
POWER. I choose wealth. I choose
influence. I CHOOSE GODLINESS. [music] I
CHOOSE THE FEAR OF THE LORD.
LISTEN.
LISTEN, [music]
look at me.
If this formula worked in getting you
born again, then it will work in getting
you healed.
>> It will work in getting you truly
delivered. Look at me. There are many of
you, if you hear what I say now, I don't
even need to pray for you for any spirit
to leave. I'm telling you, YOU CAN YOU
CAN FALL AND ROLL AND ROLL and roll.
They only react TO THE POWER OF THE
COMMAND. BUT IF YOU HAVE NOT CHOSEN,
they will leave because how forcible are
right words. But they will RETURN BACK.
YOU'RE NOT CHOOSING is permission to for
their return.
That from this day forward I choose not
to fail. How will it change? I don't
know. But let me start BY CHOOSING. WE
WORRY ABOUT TOO MANY THINGS. YOU CAN SAY
I CHOOSE TO PROSPER WHILE being
completely clueless.
I choose that in MY LIFETIME I WILL FEED
my parents. I choose that in my lifetime
I will you see that now you CAN CHOOSE
SIR. THE MEN YOU ADMIRE THEY CHOSE.
OTHERS DID NOT KNOW THEY CHOSE.
MENTORSHIP MADE THEIR CHOICE. They took
it for granted. THEY WERE SO MENTORED
[music] INTO THE CHOICE. THEY ARE NOT
AWARE THAT IT WAS A choice they made.
Let me tell you this.
The power of Jesus's dying for you is
only released when you cooperate with
that power by choosing.
The work is finished, but there are
people still going to hell today.
Now, if you ask Jesus, son of the living
God, you are seated in heaven. You are
making intercession
for the men. Why are they going to hell?
I perceive his answer will be everything
to be done for their salvation I have
done. However,
what made man to be upgraded to the God
class is not even just the glory is the
power to choose.
At the detriment of your eternal
destiny, God still left you to choose.
Is it your health? He will come and
interrupt. God is not a demon. So saying
God you are watching me like this. It
may look like a nice statement, but I'm
telling you, he will keep watching you
mercifully. When God wants to help you,
he sends a man like this preacher to let
you know, I have done everything. It's
up to you now to choose.
I set before you life and death. I set
before you. Listen,
don't allow the awareness of the grace
of God make you uncomfortable in
admitting that you chose. When you say I
chose, for many people, what it means is
that I say, "Okay, so what is THE VALUE
OF GRACE?" NO, IT WAS GRACE that
empowered me to see well to choose. But
I chose I chose. I AM SAVED BY GRACE.
BUT IT WAS THE at the instance of my
verbalizing the lordship of Jesus.
Are we together? You waste the grace of
God, you waste the wisdom of God, you
waste mentorship, you waste the ministry
of the word if you do not yield
yourself. There are many prayerful
people. YOU KNOW THAT 10 YEARS FROM NOW
THEIR LIVES MAY not change much. And I'm
telling you, it's not because prayer is
not powerful. is not because the God
they are praying to will not answer, but
it's because they do not know that
prayer forms the foundation. Fasting
forms the foundation. Coming to church
gives them, it equips them with wisdom
that comes out of knowledge. But when
all is said and done, it will have to be
up to you. That's the kind of power God
gave you. Tonight, someone can say, "I
choose that I will not walk out of here
with this sickness.
Don't just sit down and say, "I know
this man is anointed." No, you will be
surprised that if you understand my
sermon, even before we begin to pray,
you will find yourself lifting your
crotch and walking. You you saw the
testimony of the person on on the
wheelchair. You see that now a a great
distance but at the instance of the word
of God
I choose
that the devil would not oppress me
again.
The one thing God will defend with his
name uh is the power he has given you to
choose. If Satan wants to fight that
one, God will arise and say, "If you
take away the power to choose, you have
dehumanized my creation." Because what
really upgrades them to prove that he's
not wicked and selfish, he did not force
you. He would have programmed you into a
robot. A robot that executes his will.
But he cannot get glory that way. It is
the fact that he gave you the ability to
say no. And then in your saying yes is
how he's glorified because you have the
option.
Hallelujah.
Apostle but I think I've said yes and
things have not changed.
You chose but you did not decide.
You chose meaning you have found the
most profitable option but it was not
backed up by the responsibility to walk
in keeping with the principles that make
that option deliver.
Apostle I've made up my mind from today
that in the name of Jesus I will access
the anointing. That's a choice not yet a
decision. Show me your prayer life from
that day. I will see your decision. Show
me your fasting from that day. Show me
the books you are buying. Show me the
honor you have for anointed vessels.
Show me how consistent you are coming to
the house of God to learn. Every show up
in church is your decision to rise.
Every time you sing, you pray, you say,
"Amen." That's your decision to rise.
Every time you give, that's your
decision to end poverty. Every time you
listen and take notes while the word of
God is coming, I told you God's part of
it is to to bring to your life the one
you cannot do for yourself. That's why
he sent us. You see,
you may not have the anointing to get up
from that situation, but you can choose.
It's the reason why sometimes when we
pray for the sick, we ask them to do
[singing] by themselves what they could
not do. You see that now? Have you
noticed that almost 99% of the time
regardless the fact that the power of
God has been released they may not even
know they ARE HEALED IT IS AT THE POINT
WHERE they release their will
that's when the miracle comes
every time we lead you to prayer here
you know WHAT WE ARE PRAYING FOR YOU
THERE IS A PROPHETIC PART OF THE SERVICE
BUT THE PART THAT ENGAGES YOU TO USE
YOUR HEART YOUR MIND YOUR MOUTH IS
ENGAGING you to speak. You are using
your will.
You are using your will.
Tonight, God has given us another
opportunity.
His anointing is present. His sent word
is present. But my assignment is to
guide you. Some of you, you need to
bring that will part of you. It's like a
gift you have kept in a box for many
years. And you do not know that that
will
needs to work in partnership with the
spirit of God, in partnership with the
word of God to manifest your
possibilities. We are going to pray and
when it's time to pray, I'd like you to
pray sincerely from your heart and
immediately after that, I'll begin to
minister to the sick. Now, please
listen.
Every action of obedience is you
releasing your will from lifting your
hands if you are instructed to to
praying if you are instructed to
checking yourself if you are instructed
to whatever else the whatever prophetic
instruction you are giving is the
release of your will. But more
importantly when you are engaged to pray
and this includes those who are
following across the globe make sure you
pray. Those of you who are outside,
make sure when we are praying, a friend
is not nudging you and saying, "Check
this this photo." That person is
stopping you from using your will. He
doesn't have to be bad. THESE ARE THE
ways Satan stops people from receiving
in church. But the devil is a liar
tonight
>> in the name of Jesus. Everything God
told you, you will see it begin to
manifest.
>> Do you believe that? I don't know about
you, but in the name of Jesus, I am
determined that in my lifetime and that
in the shortest possible time, I will
look at everything God has told me
personally and revealed in his word and
I will not find anything missing,
anything wanting. That's my commitment.
I want you to join me in that commitment
that everything the Bible says
whatsoever he doeth, let's press for
that whatsoever dimension, don't say I
have some results. No, God wants you to
be complete. He wants you to be entire.
Rise up on your feet. Give God praise
for all that you have heard tonight.
Give God praise for all that you have
learned tonight. Outside all the
overflows, all our expressions
to our family following across the
globe. Can you thank him? Can you thank
him? Thank him.
>> [music]
>> The ignition is on. Thank him. The gear
system has been engaged. Thank him.
You've held on to the wheels. Thank him.
He's about to EMPOWER YOU TO FIRE on all
four cylinders cuz it's time for you to
soar. It's time for you to run.
And some of you here, you are not
driving a car. You are in a flight. You
happen to be that pilot. [music]
All is said and done. You are taxiing
now. It's time to fire with a level of
speed that will lift that aircraft from
where it is to where it needs to be. An
aircraft starts on the ground, but it
was meant for the sky. You don't drive
an aircraft around town. No, that's not
how it was designed. You start by
taxiing and then you get to the runway
and then you move with a speed that
makes it unfair to remain on land
[music] and then it moves. THE LAW OF
AERODYNAMICS TAKES up and you swore
40,000 ft above sea level
covering heights that are sometimes
unthinkable. Lift your voice and pray.
Lift your voice and pray.
Casting crowns, [music]
lifting hands,
bowing hearts. It's [music] what we've
come to do.
Casting rounds,
lifting hands,
bowing hearts. It's what we've come to
do. Here's the part I like. We will
[music] rise
in your name.
[music] Adon
you rain on high.
We will rise
[music] in your name.
I will
you will sing. I will rise. [music] I
will rise
in your name.
[music]
>> Prayer point number one. Say, "Father,
>> in the name of Jesus,
>> I ask for mercy. I ask your mercy
>> over the wrong choices
>> and the indecisions
>> I made decisions
>> that I have made
>> over my life
>> over my life.
>> I pray I pray
>> THAT THE BLOOD OF JESUS WILL WIPE it
away. Open your mouth and pray. Mercy
choices of dishonor.
Choices
that has swn to the flesh.
Please lift your voice and pray. Let's
start with a prayer of mercy tonight.
[music]
Someone cry like the son of David. Like
like blank batt thou [music] son of
David. Mercy over wrong choices.
Mercy over indecisions.
Mercy over poor decisions. Destiny
sabotaging [music] decisions. the things
I've said
that the birds of the air carried and
took [music] it to the future of my
destiny, programming a harvest of pain
for me [music] AND MY CHILDREN. LET THE
BLOOD SPEAK. YOU SAID I CAN COME BOLDLY
to the throne of grace
to find mercy and to obtain grace to
help in time of need. [music]
Someone lift your voice and pray.
My indecision
about [music] being vibrant spiritually.
[music] about paying attention to the
word of God.
My indecision
about consistency in learning the ways
of God. [music] I ask for mercy.
Let me not be ashamed. Oh God. [music]
Let not the devil prevail over me.
Let me not reap the consequences of
foolishness. [music]
Someone lift your voice and pray.
That's why God brought you here. [music]
Come before the throne of grace.
Obtain mercy [music] for yesterday's
indecision.
obtain mercy that THE SEEDS YOU SOLD
yesterday
that are now programming a destructive
today programming a destructive tomorrow
that by the power of God's mercy let
that tree be uprooted it was not planted
by the father
maybe the enemy did that [music]
maybe your ignorance participated in
that planting but please uproot it to
make [music] way for the planting of the
Lord that he might be glorified
[music]
in Jesus name we pray.
>> Shout this at the top of your voice.
Say, "Father,
>> Father,
>> tonight
>> I receive
>> the intelligence
>> and the wisdom
>> TO MAKE
>> SUPERIOR choices
>> and decisions in every area of my life."
Again say, "Father, tonight I receive
the intelligence and the wisdom to make
superior choices and decisions in every
area of my life." Open your mouth and
pray. The intelligence,
the wisdom that empowers me to make
superior choices
The wisdom. [music]
The wisdom.
Make sure you pray.
I receive.
[music] I manifest
your power
and your wisdom. [music]
I receive.
I manifest
your power [music]
and your wisdom.
I receive
I manifest
your power. Your praise [music] your
I receive.
I manifest in my life your power
and your [music] one more time. I
receive.
I manifest
your power
and [music] your wisdom
until the nations
[music] see Jesus
lifted up.
Exalted
till the nations [music]
see Jesus
lifted up,
glorified. [music]
I receive,
I manifest. Please pray.
Let the intelligence [music] and the
wisdom needed to influence my mind so
that I desire greatness, so that I
[music] desire victory.
I see
[music]
power
and your wisdom
unto the nations.
See Jesus [music]
lifted up
exalted.
[music] I receive.
I manifest
your power [music] and your wisdom
till the nations
see [music] Jesus
lifted up.
Glorified [music]
the intelligence and the wisdom
that moves [music] my spiritual life
forward. The intelligence and the wisdom
to learn the laws of relationships. The
intelligence and the wisdom to learn
honor as a lifestyle. The intelligence
and the wisdom to decide to be vibrant.
To decide to be prayerful
in Jesus name we pray. Prayer point
number three. Say, "Father,
>> Father,
>> in the name of Jesus,
>> in the name of
>> I receive courage,
>> I receive courage
>> to make decisions
>> that advance my life, no matter how
uncomfortable they are." Say it again.
IN THE NAME OF JESUS,
>> I receive the courage to MAKE DECISIONS
THAT ADVANCE MY LIFE NO MATTER HOW
UNCOMFORTABLE THEY ARE. LIFT your voice
and pray. The decision to cut away from
wrong companies may be uncomfortable,
but it will move your life forward.
The decision to be responsible,
will earn you persecutions. You will be
misunderstood. However, you will build
an enviable destiny.
[music]
The decision to love the house of God.
The decision to serve wholeheartedly.
[music]
>> [music]
>> In the name of Jesus. [music]
In the name of Jesus.
2 Kings chapter 20 give us verse 5 and
verse 6.
H.
return and tell Hezekiah,
the leader of my people, thus sayeth the
Lord, the God of David your father,
I have heard your prayer.
>> I have seen your tears.
>> And surely I will heal you.
>> It says, on the third day, you shall go
up to the house of the Lord. Verse six,
and I will add unto your days, Amen.
>> And I will deliver you out of this city
>> and I will defend this city.
>> Because he has heard your prayer. He
said he will heal.
>> He said he will deliver.
>> He said he will defend you.
>> I'd like you to turn this to prayer for
one minute. Lord, you have heard my
prayer. And in response to it, I cry
tonight. Let your healing power flow
through me.
Let me be completely delivered from
influences and thoughts that will not
let me rise to my prophetic destiny. And
everything that makes for my
advancement, release it over my life.
Please lift your voice.
[music]
Glory be to God.
I glory be to God.
I I glory be to God.
[music]
I I glory be to God. Hallelujah.
Hallelujah. [music]
Glory be to God.
>> Hallelujah.
Hallelujah.
Glory [music] be to God.
[music]
>> Glory be God.
Higher. [music]
Glory be to God.
[music]
>> Glory be to God. Hallelujah. [music]
Hallelujah.
Glory be to God.
[music]
>> Glory be to God.
>> [music]
>> Hallelujah. Hallelujah.
Glory be to God. Hallelujah.
Hallelujah. [music]
Glory be to God.
>> Hallelujah. [music]
I want to take a few minutes to minister
to the sick.
But in addition to ministering to the
sick, one area that I want us to contend
for tonight is this issue right from
this year. Well, it's it's something
that I found as a burden in my place of
intercession that every time I pray for
people, I keep hearing, you hear me say
it almost every service, go forward,
advance. Don't take that word for
granted. To advance means leave where
you are. You have compassed this
mountain long enough. Turn ye notwards.
Is that a good prayer?
>> Is that a good decision?
>> Do you choose to?
>> He said, tell the people that they go
forward. Don't force them. Tell them. If
they choose, then they obey. If they
refuse, I will respect it. Say, I go
forward.
>> I go forward.
>> Say I advance.
>> I advance.
>> Remember, your mouth is a declaration of
your will. Say, I go forward.
>> I go forward. Say I advance in every
area of your life. Now open up your
mouth and mention those areas one by
one. Spiritually I advance vibrant
prayer life. [music] Not like yesterday,
not like today. Vibrant word study life
in the name of Jesus. [music]
Declare over your career. I advance.
Can't be at the same level. I've
encompassed this mountain long enough. I
turn northwards. not words the place of
higher heights not words the place of
destiny [music]
someone you need to pray thank God for
the level of the anointing but it's time
to move higher it's time to move higher
[music] greater dimensions of grace
over your finances it's time to leave
the realm of lack and want going up
[music] and going down epileptic
possibilities
[music]
for someone is your health. I advance.
Tired of managing demonic [music]
satanic sicknesses.
[music]
In Jesus name we pray.
>> Please lay your hands. Let's start with
healing the sick tonight.
Why does Jesus heal? He heals because
he's love and he's merciful. Why does he
heal? To give witness to the
authenticity
of the preaching of the gospel. Uh what
happens to your body is an example of
what happens to your spirit when you
receive him. Why does he heal? to show
you how mighty he is. Healing is a
demonstration of dominion over darkness.
Why does he heal? Because he's a prayer
answering God. And he said, "For
everyone that askketh," he says, "Which
of you will your children ask for bread
and you will give them a stone? Or will
ask for fish and you will give them a
serpent? If you being evil know how to
give good gifts to your children, then
how much more will your heavenly father
give good gifts to them that ask him,
not them that want him, them that
verbalize their asking. [music] For
everyone that askketh, Matthew 7:8,
receiveth, everyone, not some, not
preachers that ask, not westerners that
ask, everyone. We have prayed and it's
important we allow the God of heaven
respond. Now please listen. Let me tell
you how healing works.
It starts with a recognition that you
need it. Not just a recognition that God
is mighty. It starts with a recognition
that you need that this state you are
bodily speaking is not the best is not
your healthiest.
I have taught you that there is a health
requirement for your spirit to remain
comfortable in your body. If your body
deterates beyond that threshold, the
spirit will have to leave. Are we
together? Every manifestation of
sickness is a ministration of death in a
measure. If it continues, eventually it
will break you down and your spirit will
have to leave.
Number two, you must believe that God is
mighty
and that he's purchased healing for you.
When we call him a healer, we mean the
one who manifests healing here and now
that's been finished in Christ. That
finished mentality is important to have
it to receive. God is not about to heal.
It's a reality that is finished. But
what will happen to you right now is
releasing your faith so that that which
is finished in Christ becomes
appropriated in your life here and now.
Do you understand?
Number three, when you believe, it's
important to know that it's always a
combination of faith and the anointing.
Your believing and the preparedness to
act is your faith part. The anointing,
you leave it to God and the vessel he's
using.
How God anointed Jesus of Nazareth with
the Holy Ghost and with power. He went
about healing by that anointing. But
Jesus never told anybody, "My anointing
makes you whole." He say your faith yet
it was the anointing. You see that now?
The Bible says God anointed him. He went
about by that anointing healing. But for
everyone we saw Jesus heal aside from
Lazarus rising from the dead, he will
say your faith that means your believing
that I'm able to and your willingness to
respond when the anointing moves is what
has made you whole.
Hallelujah. And then you take that
action of faith. So you've done your own
part of believing by coming. My own part
now is to walk in partnership with the
God of heaven and to release that
anointing. The anointing works exactly
as a drug works. Only that it works in
an accelerated way. When you swallow a
drug, they can tell you take it for 5
days, morning, afternoon, evening, and
you begin to notice the recovery. But
when the anointing gets into your body,
it has an assignment to check through
your body and scan like you do a city
scan and it finds every part of your
body that does not look like the Garden
of Eden. That becomes its assignment.
Except if your faith rejects it. If your
faith cannot believe God to go that far,
then God will walk within the limit of
the power that works in you. He's able
to do all things, but the manifestation
of that all things is limited by the
power of your mind, the power of your
believing that is at work in you.
When they said increase our faith, Jesus
told them if you have faith like a
mustard seed because faith is a living
thing. That means if the seed is there,
the way to increase your faith is not to
ask me to do it. The way to increase
your faith is to sew it and watch it
grow until it becomes great faith. He's
saying faith in you is a seed and you
can plant it and engage it until it
grows and becomes a giant oak tree.
There is no faith, there is little
faith, there is much faith, there is
great faith, there is exceeding great
faith. All these dimensions of faith
purchase various levels of
possibilities. Tonight I'm releasing my
faith with you and we're going to pray.
I'll minister to you as diverse as our
faces are. So our conditions, there are
people who are fallen from across the
globe.
When I pray with you, listen carefully.
I'll release the power of God and then I
will ask you to check yourself
and the moment you find out that there's
a miracle that's happened, take a step
of faith. If you could not walk, you
could not see, you could not hear, you
came with someone who is a lunatic or
psychosomatic in any way, an organ in
your body. If it's a part of your body
you cannot touch, you just place your
hand anywhere. Look beyond the man and
look at the God who is moving in the
midst of his people. Moses was
stretching the rod. God was breathing on
the sea. The Bible says he parted the
the Red Sea with the breath of his
nostrils. Exodus chapter 15. And yet it
was the rod of Moses. As soon as Moses
was placing the rod like I'm speaking
now that's akin to the rod, but there is
the breath of the almighty breathing
through your mortal body and bringing
you quickening.
We'll do that very quickly. Now there
are several overflows here and for sake
of time as soon as you find out that
there's a miracle I'm going to give you
an opportunity to check yourself. The
moment that happens, whether you are
outside any of the overflows or online
so that we save time, leave your seat
immediately when I do ask you, you can
come and stand to my left or stand to my
right. You are about to testify of the
wonder working power of Jesus Christ.
Something happened to you that shown
improvement or perfection of your body.
You walk out quickly. So that whilst
that is happening, I'll be ministering
deliverance to the captives and we'll be
releasing breakthrough and in no time by
the grace of God, we'll be able to walk
within the time we have and see the much
that God will help us do. Hallelujah.
Place your hand. Let me pray for you.
Thou art welcome in [singing] this
place. Holy Spirit, thou art welcome in
this place. Omnipotent
Father of mercy and grace, thou art
welcome in this place.
[music]
The one is
my ra.
Oh.
[music]
Oh. [music]
Oh.
[music]
Now in the name of Jesus with your hands
placed wherever you are trusting God for
is your eyes place your hand there your
head place your hand there if there's a
part of your body you cannot touch just
make contact with your chest apostle can
I stand in for someone absolutely for my
loved ones absolutely
can I lift up the picture of someone who
is sick that I came here with absolutely
can I connect someone online to receive
his healing absolutely apostle I'm in
the hospital. Can I put the visuals for
the patients? Absolutely. This is a
business of the power of Jesus flowing
from here across the nations. And then
agree with me as I begin to pray. Make
sure your eyes are on Jesus, I learned
from Pastor Beni Hinn that the more you
take your eyes away from the sickness
and the infirmity that plagues you and
you just see Jesus bringing you healing,
you will eventually find out that that
sickness is gone. But when your
attention
is on it and how big it is and how
impossible it is, you see, and then go
back to the former progression and then
you'll find out that it will affect you
and you will not be able to receive.
Praise the name of Jesus. So place your
hand there. Thank you Jesus.
Place your hand there.
Oh,
oh,
[music]
oh.
Oh [music]
my God, I sense the healing anointing.
Oh
Jehovah Rafa,
the one who heals. I will bring you
health and I will bring you cure.
[music]
Oh.
Oh
[music]
[music] do
thundering [music]
do [singing]
the one
[music]
>> in the name of Jesus.
Shout a believing amen in the name of
Jesus.
Right now, I rebuke every spirit of
infirmity,
every devil,
every yoke,
every altar,
and every covenant that's [music]
responsible for sicknesses, for
diseases, for infirmities. I [music]
decree and declare by the power that
raised Christ from the dead, let the
anointing s through your body right now.
Let the anointing sush through your body
right now. Let the anointing sush
through your body right now. Let the
anointing sush through your body right
now. Bringing cleansing, bringing
wholeness, bringing healing, cleansing,
wholeness, healing in the name of Jesus
Christ. In the name of Jesus Christ. In
the name of Jesus Christ. In the name of
Jesus Christ, I decree and declare by
the power of the Holy Spirit from the
crown of your head to the soles of your
feet, BE HEALED IN JESUS' NAME.
BE HEALED IN JESUS' NAME.
EYE CONDITIONS BE HEALED IN JESUS' NAME.
DEAF EARS BE OPENED IN JESUS' NAME.
CANCER BE HEALED IN JESUS' NAME.
Everyone who COULD NOT WALK, BEGIN TO
WALK IN JESUS' NAME. Who could not talk,
BEGIN TO TALK IN JESUS' NAME. WHO COULD
NOT SEE, BEGIN TO SEE IN JESUS' NAME.
Who could not hear, BEGIN TO HEAR IN
JESUS' NAME. EVERY PAIN AROUND YOUR
BODY, I COMMAND IT TO GIVE WAY IN THE
NAME OF JESUS.
LET IT GIVE WAY IN THE NAME OF JESUS.
The Lord is showing me the vision of a
pregnant woman. I don't know what
problem that is, but there you are you
are about maybe 6 months there about
pregnant. I don't know if you are here
or following online and I'm seeing that
you're having a medical condition
um that the baby has shifted. The baby
is not in the correct position. In the
name of Jesus, I decree and declare, let
there be a rearrangement of that baby
now,
by the power of the Holy Spirit.
All kinds of blood conditions in the
name of Jesus be healed.
Everything damaging your blood,
destroying your blood, the Bible says
the life of the flesh is in the blood. I
bring you life and healing right now.
Life and healing right now.
life and healing right now. Life and
healing right now in the name of Jesus.
You could not move your limbs, move them
now.
You could not bend over, [music] begin
to bend now. Every organ that's failing
or that's failed in Jesus name we
command that organ, let life sudge into
it right now.
[music] Bone conditions be healed now.
Blood conditions be healed now.
Organs be restored now.
There's someone you've been having
recurrent fever. Right now you are
feeling very feverish. You came here in
the name of Jesus. Like Peter healed um
like Jesus healed Peter's mother-in-law.
I declare be healed right now.
be cured from that fever in Jesus name.
[music] Someone is having sugar diabetes
in the name of Jesus be healed.
Hepatitis be healed.
Ulcers be healed
in the name of Jesus. The Lord is
showing me someone you are watching from
Niger state. Your leg is rotten. Your
leg is rotten. You literally can see the
bones in the name of Jesus. Niger state,
I decree and declare be healed right now
by the power of the Holy Ghost. If you
came here using a walking aid and you
could not move in the name of Jesus, let
the life of God s through your body, I
declare that you begin to walk right
now. Begin to walk unaded right now.
Begin to walk right now. You could not
move your hands. Begin to move your
hands. Every lump in your breast or any
part of your body, I command it to give
way right now.
The Lord is showing me a lady who has a
cyst. This This is not outside of your
womb area. This is inside your womb
area. It's caused severe bleeding.
Severe bleeding right now. And pain,
severe pain. But the power of God is
touching you right now. and he's
bringing you life and he's bringing you
healing
>> in the name of Jesus.
>> In the name of Jesus,
>> the Lord is showing me someone. Your
father, you are watching from
Manchester. You're watching from
Manchester. Your father has a condition
they call dementia where I think he
forgets and all of that loses. He cannot
easily identify people. In the name of
Jesus Christ, we declare restoration of
his consciousness, his sanity and
coherence in Jesus name.
In Jesus name, there's someone you have
a problem smelling. I'm praying for you
by the power of the Holy Spirit. Let
your sense of smell be restored.
Let it be restored.
>> The Lord is I'm hearing in my my spirit
appendicitis
in Jesus name. We command healing right
now.
We command healing right now. We command
healing right now. Someone has a severe
pain around not your kneecap, your lap,
your entire lap area has a burning
sensation. In the name of Jesus, I bring
you life and healing.
>> Are you still receiving? Say amen.
>> The Lord has shown me this case before.
I've ministered this a number of times.
You are a lady here. You are not a
nursing mother yet. You are lactating.
You are producing milk. You are not a
nursing mother yet you are producing
milk. In the name of Jesus, I declare
may your body be restored
right now be restored.
High blood pressure be healed.
Low blood pressure be healed.
Heat around your body, movement around
your body be healed right now.
In the name of Jesus Christ. There's
someone you have a problem with sleep.
No matter how rested you seem you are
once you lie down to sleep you unable to
sleep. I declare may the Lord bring you
deliverance right now
in the name of Jesus Christ. Burning
sensation around the hand. This is not
just an operation of the anointing. This
is this is something that is medical.
You feel numbness. Numbness. I'm hearing
that numbness. It's as if the the the
initial signs of stroke numbness because
the same thing is happening um on your
your limbs in the name of Jesus. I
command stroke to go now.
Stroke to go now.
The inability to walk and stand. I bring
you life right now in Jesus name. Now
whether I mention your case or not,
provided you came here trusting God for
healing, I shout it as you receive. Be
healed.
I shout it as you receive. Be healed.
Be healed.
BE HEALED.
Pray for one minute. Say, "I receive my
healing." Go ahead and begin to check
yourself in the name of Jesus. Begin to
check yourself right now very quickly.
You [music] could not move move your
hands. You could not walk. Go ahead and
begin to check yourself. Lift your crush
or wheelchair, whatever you came with,
and begin [music] to walk. You could not
hear, begin to test yourself. You could
not see, begin to see in the name
[music] of Jesus Christ. Make sure you
do what you could not do before in Jesus
muchless name we pray. Now for everyone
whether you are outside, whether you are
inside, I want you to check yourself. I
want to minister deliverance right now.
While that is happening, the moment you
see that a miracle has happened, the
lump is gone. Now, for some of you, you
may need to verify with the medical
stand, uh if you don't know where the
medical stand is, especially for those
outside. You can come in and you'll be
directed to the medical stand. They are
ready. There are doctors qualified to
test you. And the moment you see that
there's a miracle, others, you've
already checked yourself. You've seen
that the pain is gone. You can see, you
can hear, you can walk. Wherever you
are, please leave your seat. If you are
coming from outside, tell the ushers or
tell the protocol, I'm coming to testify
and they'll allow you. Same with all the
overflows. For those who have received
miracles across the globe, I'm sure that
the line will be posted um just just
just put for you so that you can have it
and then send it very quickly. Let's
have the testimonies. Those who are
inside here, make sure you make your way
out. There are doctors who are
positioned right now. Let's celebrate
them as they come in the name of Jesus.
Check yourself.
Check yourself and come out quickly.
While that is on, while they are coming,
let me quickly minister deliverance. I
see a mother coming. Are you celebrating
miracles? God is touching people. Praise
the name of the Lord. Make sure you
don't sit back. You can follow any of
the aisles inside, outside, do what you
couldn't do. As soon as the power of God
touches you, you make your way out and
um I mean miracles are happening
everywhere. We give Jesus praise. Now
very quickly, very quickly, let me
minister deliverance. What is
deliverance?
Where the supernatural power of God
comes into your life and brings a
separation between you and unclean
spirits and between you and unfavorable
conditions. Deliverance is not only
limited to the exiting of spirit. It can
be a separation between you and
conditions that are antichrist. Are you
celebrating miracles already happening?
But now let's pray for those who are
oppressed of the devil. How God anointed
Jesus of Nazareth and he went about
doing good, healing all they that were
oppressed. I'm going to ask you to shout
the name Jesus. And we shout that name
for a reason. It is so that the nations
will know that the one who heals, who
delivers, who saves is Jesus, the son of
the living God. Are we together now? And
as we shout that name, there are some of
you who have been victims of all kinds
of demonic orchestrations, plaguing
families, all kinds of satanic
manipulations. That's why he brought you
here. and from the front to the back,
the left to the right, all the
overflows. And those who are following
online, as I make these declarations
prophetically, the power of God will
surge like rain, like fire, it will rest
upon you, and God will bring you
deliverance. If you believe that, say,
"Amen."
>> Like fire, like rain, let your glory
fall. Like fire, like rain. Let it fall.
Like fire, like rain, [music]
like rain. Let your glory
fall like fire. Like [music] rain. Let
it fall
like fire. Like rain [music]
like rain. Let your glory
fall [music] like fire. Miracles are
happening everywhere.
[music]
Like fire, like rain,
like rain.
[music]
High
fire.
What in the world is this?
[music and cheering] This is a pleasant
surprise.
For those of you who don't know why
we're rejoicing, we have an August
surprise right here.
>> [cheering and music]
>> This is the sound of revival.
Let's go. Come on, give Jesus praise.
[music]
Like fire, like rain.
Like rain, let your glory
fall. [music]
Like fire, like rain, let it fall.
Hallelujah. [music]
In the name of Jesus,
>> I want ushers to bring them out very
quickly. The power of God is going to be
resting on people, families. The Bible
says, "But upon Mount Zion, there shall
be deliverance and there shall be
holiness and the sons of Jacob shall
possess their possessions." At the count
of three, I want you to shout Jesus.
As you shout that name, everything
that's not of God that held [music] you
bound must let you go. Must let you go.
Who is ready? At the count of three. 1 2
3. Shout Jesus.
In the name [music] of Jesus. Every
altar breaks now. Every yoke gives
[music] way right now by the power of
the Holy Ghost. by the power of the Holy
Ghost, bring them out very quickly in
the name of Jesus.
[music] Every demonic thing holding you
down, YOLKS OF ANCESTRY, TYING DOWN,
FAMILIES, tying [music] down,
I decree and declare by the anointing of
the Holy Ghost, BE DELIVERED NOW.
BE SET FREE NOW. BE DELIVERED NOW.
BE SET FREE NOW.
THE YOLKS THAT PLAGUE THE FIRSTBORN, THE
YOLKS THAT PLACE THE ONES WHO OPEN UP
THE WOMB, I PRAY for you. Anyone who's
under this bondage,
be set free now.
Bring them out. BE SET FREE NOW.
BE SET FREE NOW.
I'm seeing chains in my visions. Chains
that have held people bound in the name
of Jesus. Whether you an usher or not,
when someone is under the anointing,
please help them. The ushers are limited
because of the size. I decree and
declare right now, everyone held back
with chains of darkness. EVERYONE DIED
DOWN, be released now.
BE RELEASED NOW.
BE RELEASED NOW. BE RELEASED NOW. BE
RELEASED NOW.
EVERYONE SAY, "FATHER,
IN THE NAME OF JESUS, AND BY THE BLOOD,
I DECLARE I AM FREE." OPEN YOUR MOUTH
AND PRAY IN ONE MINUTE. FREE.
UNQUESTIONABLY FREE.
FREE.
Free
indeed.
Free.
[music]
Hallelujah.
Praise the name of the Lord.
Now I'm going to pray families that have
been in a state of retrogression that
you don't go forward. I want to prophesy
AND AS I DECLARE THAT FIRE will rest on
you. Once it rest on you in the name OF
JESUS, YOUR DESTINY will open up. I
DECREE AND DECLARE EVERYONE WHO'S been
bound, THE SPIRIT OF DELAY, THE SPIRIT
OF RETROGRESSION SHALL BREAK AS YOU
SHOUT JESUS, LET THAT DOOR OPEN NOW.
SHOUT JESUS.
Let the [music] doors be open. Let the
doors be open. LET THE DOORS BE OPEN.
IN THE NAME OF JESUS. Be open. Be open.
Be open.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Come on. Hallelujah.
>> There's someone bearing my name. Your
name is Joshua.
The Lord is saying I'm ending captivity.
You are from Ki state. Joshua, who is
that? You are from Ki state. Come.
Deliverance comes for you now. Joshua
from co be careful be careful my friend
listen listen don't injure the people
you are receiving your old Joshua from
where
>> in the name of Jesus not only will God
deliver you the [music] call of God is
upon your life he will make you a mighty
vessel I release grace I decree AND
DECLARE OUT OF HIM NOW THE NAME of Jesus
out of him by the power of the Holy
Ghost in the name of Jesus Christ I'm
hearing a name Rachel
Rachel and the Lord is saying your
season of restoration. You are entering
your season. I don't know who that is.
Rachel, the power of God is on you.
Rachel, Rachel, you are wearing like a
red dress. Rachel, the power of God is
on you. I'm seeing this in my vision. I
will pray for every Rachel. But there is
a Rachel. The power of God is you are
wearing like a red dress. Please find
that person for me. Ushers. Rachel.
Da da da.
Okay. Ushers, they're [music] showing
you. Is there someone like that? Rachel,
bring her. Bring her.
[music]
I'm hearing another name. Auba. Auba.
Auba. Your name is Auba.
The Lord wants to take the plague of
death. I will pray for Rachel. What God
says to one, he says to all. Let me pray
for every Rachel here in the name of
Jesus. Everything stopping you.
The Lord is showing me a vision over
Rachel. I'm seeing an egg that is
breaking. That means it's time for you
to emerge from your place of hiding. I
release that grace right now over Rachel
in the name of Jesus. I release that
grace right now. I want to pray for the
one under the anointing wearing red. I
saw a red um if there's somebody like
that, please let me know.
In the name of Jesus Christ. In the name
of Jesus Christ.
[music] Bolu. B O L U. Euroba name.
Bolu. Is there someone with that name?
Polo,
I'm seeing you inside an aircraft
and I'm seeing you moving to another
country. This is what I'm seeing. I
don't know you, my brother, but I'm
seeing you inside an aircraft. You see,
let me tell you this. Look up, please.
Every time God gives a prophetic word,
it takes three things for prophecy to
happen. Number one, an awareness of what
God is saying. Number two, an accurate
interpretation of what he's saying.
Number three, the timing that coincides
with his will. Knowing what God has said
and knowing the timing are two different
things. Who is Auba? There's no Auba
here. You are Yuba. I want to pray for
you. The Lord wants to break something
from Southern Kaduna.
Southern Kaduna. Sometimes God opens my
eyes and supernaturally I decree and
declare Southern Kaduna by the power of
the Please don't come out. I'm not
asking you to come out yet so that there
will be we need to be fast here. Bolu
who is Bolu in the name of Jesus I pray
for you Bolu I see you in an aircraft
those please if you are if you are
coming for testimony come this way we'll
take a few testimonies there are
miracles happening please make sure you
move to my right or to my left my right
or my left don't stand here for miracles
to the right there's still some space
there you can move some of the people
here so that there'll be an even
distribution
bolu
In the name of Jesus, I pray for you.
It's time to come out of your place of
hiding. By the power of the Holy Spirit,
I release you. Let light shine on you.
Let light shine on you. Let light shine
on you. Let light shine on you in the
name of Jesus Christ.
I'm hearing the number 25. Listen to me,
please. I'm hearing the number 25 and
I'm seeing like a crown that is being
placed on the heads of people. I believe
that this sounds for honor 25. This is
happening to people everywhere. That
grace, that mantle for honor. Wherever
you are, I decree AND DECLARE, LET THAT
CROWN,
[music]
let it rest on your head in the name of
Jesus Christ that you will be a royal
diadem in the hands of our God. 25.
THAT'S WHAT I'M HEARING in my spirit.
Let that crown rest upon your head in
the name of Jesus Christ. [music]
[screaming]
All those who are under the anointing
here, I declare the spirits that oppress
you [music] by the power of the Holy
Ghost be set free right now by the blood
of Jesus. We declare your liberty. By
the blood of Jesus, we declare you free
in the name of Jesus. Please return back
to your seat. Now hear me please. The
Lord wants to bring deliverance to
southern um sometimes God opens my eyes
and just shows me the territory. So glad
and honored to have pastor Nath here.
I'm going to ask you there. The spirit,
please listen. The spirit of death of
backwardness,
DEATH AND BACKWARDNESS WHERE PEOPLE die
before their time and people never
whether they are educated or not, it
looks like they never rise in life. If
that has happened to you, you are part
of that. Make your way quickly. Come and
stand in front here. Southern Kaduna, I
want to pray for you very quickly. at
the blast of the trumpet we are going to
pray [music]
and that everything that is not of God
it must give way is called a miracle
service please if you're coming make it
very quick the spirit of
>> [music]
[music]
>> Yahe
above
Yahe.
[music]
Yahe
above
Yahe.
Yahweh.
Yahe
above.
>> [music]
>> Southern Kuna.
Southern Kuna. [music]
[music]
Yahe [music]
reveal reveal
your glory. [music]
[music]
>> [music]
>> I am come that ye may have life and have
it more abundantly, [music]
more abundantly,
more abundantly.
[music]
Now in the name of Jesus, look at me. My
dear brothers and sisters, listen. When
God makes a call like this, it may not
necessarily be about the individual. It
is about the territory and the family.
Are we together? Yes.
I believe in the power of God. God
delivers territories. He sent Jonah to
Nineveh. Nineve Jonah chapter 3. It was
not the salvation of an individual. It
was the salvation of a territory. Jonah
was sent to Nineveh. God was interested
in the entire territory. And the Bible
says from the king to the beasts
in the name of Jesus. Every family
connected to this territory that's under
the sway of darkness, untimely death,
and the retrogression of men, we come by
the help that lady. WE COME BY THE
BLOOD. AS YOU SHOUT THE NAME JESUS, WE
DECREE [music] and declare every altar
enchantments OF DARKNESS BY THE BLOOD OF
JESUS. We declare victory. At the count
of three, shout Jesus. 1 2 3.
Be delivered now. Be delivered now. NOW
BE SET FREE. Be set free. [music] Be set
free. We speak to the earth. release the
destinies of these men in the name of
Jesus. [music]
Men and women, male and female, spirits
of untimely death, [music]
it comes to an end. The lion has
prevailed in the name of Jesus.
[music] In the name of Jesus.
Now I speak over you by the power of the
Holy Ghost. everything that is not of
God connected to your bloodline because
you are in Christ in the name of Jesus
and in partnership with your will. I
declare you delivered now.
DELIVERED NOW
BY THE BLOOD. DELIVERED NOW. LET THERE
BE RESTORATION.
DELIVERED NOW. LET THERE BE restoration
of dignity of jobs IN THE NAME OF JESUS.
[music]
Please return back to your seat. It's
amazing how God has used the foolishness
of the gospel.
King eternal,
[music]
King immortal.
You're the King invisible. [music]
The only wise God. King eternal. King
eternal.
King immortal. [music]
You're the king invisible.
The only one star. [music]
King eternal. Save eternal.
King immortal. [music and singing]
King invisible.
>> [music]
>> The only one is God.
>> I'm hearing a name Asab.
Asabe. I that should be another name. I
know it to be another name. Asabe. Very
quickly. We'll take the testimonies, but
I'm hearing the name Asab. And one more
prayer and then we'll take the
testimonies. I'm hearing in my spirit
recovery. Usually I will hear
restoration, but I'm hearing recovery.
as
praise the name of the Lord.
>> Hallelujah.
>> If that is your name, let me just speak.
I'm hearing recovery. Usually, I would
hear restoration, but I'm hearing
recovery in [music] the name of Jesus
Christ. Everything that needs to be
recovered,
things, time, opportunities,
relationships, by the power that raised
Christ from the dead
as you can come join them very quickly.
In the name that is above all names, I
speak over your life.
Will you believe? What?
I'm having a vision
and in this vision I'm seeing a
gathering and in this gathering I'm
seeing a woman carrying twins, children.
This is what I'm seeing.
This is like a baby dedication.
When God brings forth visions like this,
it is to reveal something he wants to
do. In the name of Jesus, I stretch my
hands. Let me pray for a bay first. I
pray for all of you. Whatever it is
that's been lost, that needs to be
recovered. I stretch my hands by the
power of the Holy Spirit. You have come
in response to this word. Let it be your
testimony now. Let it be your testimony
now. RECOVERY. THE SPIRIT THAT BIND
PEOPLE and keep people bound. I declare
it gives way right now. I speak recovery
by the anointing of the Holy Ghost. In
the name of Jesus Christ, I want to pray
for fruitfulness based on the vision God
just showed me. I saw a gathering like a
baby celebration and I'm seeing twins.
I'm seeing a basket with two children
there. Can I pray that prayer?
Don't despise prophesyings. Are we
together? I want to pray for you. Pastor
Nat, can I ask you to blow and pastor
Nat is going to blow. I don't know who
this concerns whether fruitfulness in
terms of children, fruitfulness in terms
of career or business advancement. That
means everything that is not yielding.
Jesus caused the fig tree because there
was no I I know that we are seeing
babies now, but I believe it applies to
every area of life. As pastor Nath blows
in the name of Jesus, I'm releasing my
faith with you. Your mind is a womb.
Your womb is a womb. Are we together?
Everything that is a womb that will not
be with child, we are when you release
the power of God that you begin to
produce. Yes, sir.
[music]
In the name of Jesus Christ,
let wombs [music] open. Let wombs open.
Let wombs open to be fruitful. Let wombs
open to be fruitful. Let wombs open to
be fruitful. Let wombs open to be
fruitful [music]
biologically. Be fruitful financially.
Be fruitful in terms of your thinking.
be fruitful. Let me say that again.
Biologically be fruitful. Everyone here
trusting God for the fruit of the womb,
I decree and declare, may the God of
mercy surprise you.
May the God of [music] mercy surprise
you
in the name of Jesus.
I pray for every dead dying finances by
the power of the Holy Ghost. Let the
womb of your mind be empowered to
produce
in the name of Jesus.
Please be seated. Let's take a few
testimonies very quickly. Let's take a
few testimonies. By the way, how many of
you have come here with your prayer
requests? Let me see your hands lifted.
Okay. Very quickly, while we are taking
the testimony, please listen
attentively. We're going to celebrate
Jesus Christ. And um once we're done, we
receive the testimonies. I mean, we
receive the prayer requests very
quickly. very quickly. Yes, sir. Please.
>> All right. So, Apostle, this our dear
sister bridged in here with some level
of speed that
>> I saw her rejoicing and smiling.
>> Yes. So, she's had this pain since
January.
>> A fracture.
>> A fracture actually. And
>> a fracture.
>> Please, you can come with just come.
>> So, you see the the the scar from that
injury.
>> So, I fractured my Okay. I fractured my
ankle January and since then um I've
been trying to get healing and I've been
limping and praying and asking God to
help me you know. So today I even came
in the morning I worked I was telling
God today is the day I will not go
before daddy started um speaking on
decision and choice. I said today I'm
not going anywhere with this thing.
That's right. I have come and I will go
out.
>> And now what happened to you? So
immediately after you finish praying, I
ran out cuz I was upstairs. I want I ran
from here up there. I couldn't do it
before. Now
>> look at this.
In the name of Jesus. A fractured a
fractured knee or limb in the name of
Jesus. We declare perfection for you by
the power of the Holy Spirit in Jesus
name. Are you celebrating miracles? Yes
sir. Next person please. and our dear
sister here for almost a month now has
actually been having problem with her
knees.
>> Her knee?
>> Yes.
>> So um almost a month I've had this
severe pain in my left knee. I can't
really do a lot of stuff. I can't bend
because standing up from the bed is like
okay
>> a hassle. So yeah whilst you were
praying I already told myself that I'm
just waiting for you to finish so that
I'll come and give my testimony. I was
not feeling better yet but the moment
you said check yourself I just knew I
was feeling okay and then I came out. I
cannot cross my leg before but now
>> but now you're able to
>> comfortably
>> in the name of Jesus perfection for you
by the power of the Holy Spirit in Jesus
name. Let's celebrate Jesus.
>> So Apostle here we have Christopher
>> Christopher
>> he's a gym instructor and for since
January he had a problem with his knees
affected his ability to train others.
Yeah, since January this year, I I
started feeling this pain. Whenever I
bend [music] during during my workouts
in the gym, I feel the pain. So when we
were praying and after the prayer, I say
we should check ourel and I tried to
bend twice. I feel I didn't feel the
pain.
>> Check yourself now, sir.
>> Any pain? Any pain?
>> I'm okay, sir.
>> Any pain?
>> So those of you looking for a gym
instructor, your instructor is healed.
May God bless you in the name of Jesus
Christ. Amen. Can we have a few there?
Go ahead,
>> Apostle. There's mighty miracle here.
Our sister had accident two years ago.
She had her left leg fractured. The
tigu. So fractures again.
>> Yes, fractures. So she was using the
medical head. But last year, you know,
she dropped that, but she was still
having pain in her leg. Now there's a
metal inserted in the in this leg.
>> There's a metal in the leg.
>> Yes. And then they have also given us
this shoe to head her movement. But now
the power of God has touched her. The
pain has disappeared. Now she could
stoop, you know,
>> with the metal
>> with the metal in the leg. The pain has
disappeared.
>> I'm not a doctor, but look at this.
>> And now she can even remove the shoe and
walk.
>> Remove the shoe and move.
Ah, look at this. [cheering]
>> There's a metal in her leg.
She used to limp before.
>> Oh. Oh.
>> Oh, you use the shoe.
>> I tried. My friend was up there, so she
was the one that helped me. I said, "Let
me try." I I removed the shoe because
mostly that shoe helped me with pain.
Oh, I see. I use wage shoe. I couldn't
walk like this. Even in my house, I
would be in pain a little bit because
right now
>> I can see everything. [singing]
[music]
>> Come on, someone.
See everything.
Heat. Heat. [music]
[music]
mighty.
Don't listen listen don't worry. Now
that pastor has looked for trouble,
he will be the one to wrap up the
service.
Hallelujah. I'll just share the grace
and allow where our hallelujah challenge
will go. Okay.
Okay.
So
when when when we are done worship team
I hope you are ready.
>> Okay. Praise the name of the Lord. Let
every man abide in his calling. Let me
be done casting out demons so that I get
out of the way and let pastor not blow
up this place. But the next testimony
very quickly miracle here.
>> Yes, please. You're not just see this
our brother of insanity.
>> Insanity.
>> Yes, sir.
>> He came here mad.
>> Yes. For the past two years. TWO YEARS.
SISTER IS HERE.
>> THAT'S A SISTER.
>> THAT'S a sister.
[music]
SIR, THEY DISCOVERED AS YOU WERE
TEACHING, he started saying some things
that were they were not.
>> Let us speak. Let me hear.
>> SO THE SISTER NOW CALLED HE STARTED
CALLING THE SISTERS BY THEIR NAME.
>> Come on. Look at this.
>> Hallelujah.
>> Very quickly.
>> Praise the Lord. Okay. My brother here
has been under spiritual attacks for
years. But last week's Sunday, it's got
worse. He's a chronic member of Coonia.
He never misses a Sunday.
>> He miss the only Sunday he missed was
last week when the attack took place.
>> What happened now?
>> For seven days. He could not eat. He
could not speak. Sometimes he will just
be still as if he's dead. We brought him
here bound both hand and foot. You you
bound him here.
>> Bound bound.
>> Lose him and let him go. Come on.
Lose him and let him go of the universe.
[music]
What can you do?
What can you [music] do? Look at this.
Jesus.
Turn around. Turn around my friend.
[music]
What you say?
What can you [music] say
Jesus?
You are able
[music]
mighty God. You are
Jesus. There is nothing. There is no
[music]
>> [music]
>> Heat. Heat.
[music and singing]
>> [music]
>> Jesus.
He was tied and brought here
on
his side with us.
Tied and brought here [music] in the
name of Jesus. Everything that's bound
in the order of Lazarus,
bringing Lazarus TO DEAD WAS JESUS'S
ASSIGNMENT. but losing him and let him
go. He told the man, in the name of
Jesus, I declare everything that's
bound, let it be loose right now. Lose
right now. Lose right now. Lose right
now.
[music]
My friend, what's your name?
>> What's your name?
>> Where are you now? Right now.
>> I'm I'm in Habuja.
>> Right here. Where are you in this place?
>> Jesus.
[music] You have
Jesus
[music] in your special way. What was
impossible?
You made possible
Jesus. [music]
Let's celebrate them. Let's celebrate
that very people.
>> [music]
>> Yes sir. My goodness.
Apostle.
My God.
>> Okay. Who? Okay. Let's do one here and
then please very quickly.
>> Two years back pain and abdominal pain.
Healed by the power of God.
>> Two years back pain.
>> She had surgery.
>> She had a surgery where?
>> Yes sir.
>> 2022. And now
>> they pray even immediately
pray
even they come I GO TO I wantit vomit no
come IMMEDIATELY COME THEY PRAY THEY
PRAY JUST STOP DISTURB me even THE WEST
JUST DISAPPEAR like that
>> gone completely thank you Jesus thank
you Jesus you are healed my dear
completely never returns to you again in
Jesus name pastor takes. Yes, sir.
>> It's well, sir.
>> Okay. Go ahead.
>> So, Sashi, she's been having this
headache and fever for like 3 days.
Okay. And when you spoke a word about
those fever and headaches.
>> Yes. I was even contemplating on going
to the medical stand so that they will
give me a stronger and digestive because
all the ones I've been taking, they are
not working.
>> It's not working.
>> And I said, okay, since today is miracle
service, I will wait and connect my
faith. And right now I am open
>> completely gone in the name of Jesus.
Perfected by the power of the Holy
Spirit in Jesus name. God bless you.
>> Apostle this dear finel looking
gentleman. Yes
>> has been having a neck pain for 3 years.
Neck pain?
>> Yes. His neck for 3 years.
>> So I've been having this neck pain for 3
years. So last during May the neck pain
in school just left after I received
prayers. It left but all of a sudden
it's it's no longer there. I came I came
here today with the neck pain. I was
just feeling it. I was feeling
distressed left and right. Left and
right.
>> No pain
>> in the name of Jesus Christ. We declare
perfection for you by the power of the
Holy Spirit. Yes, please.
>> Apostle, she she she has had pain in her
hands for 3 days. When you made the word
of knowledge, she came out to the line
and said it had reduced. So when we took
her testimony, she said it had reduced.
By the time we walked to the front and
went back, it had gone
>> completely.
>> We bind the spirit of stroke.
>> Amen.
>> In the name of Jesus, do what you
couldn't do. Your hands just like this.
>> Totally gone completely
>> in the name of Jesus. Perfection for
you. Amen.
>> By the power of the Holy Spirit.
>> Amen.
>> In Jesus name.
>> Amen. Next person please.
>> So our brother here has had this pain in
the left side of his chest.
>> Yes sir.
>> So uh 2024 I went to the hospital. They
did ECD test for me and they said it was
normal. Then last year again I did it
was normal again. But when I was coming
here today driving I was still feeling
the pain.
>> But when I got here and you were praying
I just felt like what I could not do
like I could not really breathe very
well. But now if you want me to try I
can try. Sir,
>> you're a good actor. God bless you.
You've discovered your talent in this
place. So add it to what you you've been
doing. May God bless you. Let's
celebrate him.
>> Hallelujah. Yes, please. Our our dear
sister here had been skipping for a
while and she said she was trying a new
technique on one foot. Yes. And she hurt
herself. Um she's been having that pain.
And when you prayed for people with
injuries, you know, fractures and all
that.
>> Yes. So before you started praying, I
even checked if the pain was still there
and it was there. But after even during
the prayer, I was checking checking was
not there. On this line, I've been
checking even coming down the staircase.
I've been pressing my leg and it's gone.
In the name of Jesus,
>> we decree over you by the power of the
Holy Ghost.
>> It is gone perfected forever in Jesus
name.
>> Apostle two years back pain healed by
the power of God.
>> Back pain.
>> Back pain
>> in the name of Jesus.
>> She came here with these are these are
causing sister.
>> Okay. May God bless all of you. By the
way, let me pause for a moment. May God
bless all of you who encourage your
loved ones by coming with them to
church. It's one thing to invite them,
but it's another thing. You notice that
some of the people like the the
gentleman who was mad. Now, imagine if
the sister was tired today and didn't
come to church and didn't bring him to
church. You see that? Now, it's a reason
why it's not only important to invite
people to church. I was glad when they
said unto me, let us not go, let us
together go to the house of the Lord.
Hallelujah. So, perfection for you, my
dear. You are made whole in Jesus name.
Next person.
>> Daddy, you gave a word of knowledge of a
woman with a pain in her lap.
>> Yes.
>> Immediately you gave that word of
knowledge. The power of God touched her
and then the pain disappeared.
>> How long has it been?
>> Sir, for more than a month I went to the
hospital. They give me drugs. I've been
taking I could not sleep every day night
and even this my hand for more than 20
years that I had that
>> more than 20 years. Yes sir. What could
you do?
>> I cannot ship. I cannot IS VERY FLEX.
FOR MORE than 20 years. Yes, sir. And
now,
>> now look at it. Look at it. Look at it.
Jesus has done it. I give God the glory.
>> In the name of Jesus, I pray for you.
Perfection for your hands, your limbs,
and every part of your body. You are
made whole this moment [music] in Jesus
name we pray. Very quickly, next person.
One year backbone healed by the power of
God. She said after she had her third
child, they said one of the bones
shifted and so she has had difficulty in
her waist. But now as she minister, the
power of God touched her and now she can
>> Where was the pain, ma'am?
>> My spine here.
>> Right there. And now
>> it's not pain.
>> Do what you couldn't do. Can you bend
left, right, up, down, completely gone.
Let's celebrate what Jesus is doing.
Praise the name of the Lord. Yes,
please.
>> Apostle lump in the breast disappeared
by the power of God.
>> Lump in the breast. They have two
doctors have checked her and they not
>> examine her. Come on, let's give Jesus
praise.
Everything that oppressed you, you will
not find it again.
>> Are you receiving? Say a loud amen.
>> Yes, please.
>> 11 years pain in the kneel healed by the
power of God. He had an accident and
fell on a bike.
>> Which of them left or right?
>> And now go ahead. Do what you enable to
do.
[music]
This this man looks physically fit. Do
you play football?
>> Gymnastics
>> at Oh, gymnastics. I see. We have a lot
of I think very soon maybe we'll start
aerobics in Coonia. Hallelujah. God
bless you. I declare perfection for your
body. Amen.
>> In Jesus matchless name we pray. Uh
okay, let's let's take one more there.
One more.
>> Backbone healed to you by the power of
God.
>> Okay, there are just two of them left.
So, let's just take the two.
>> Okay. And then our auntie here. Migraine
headache. migraine headache
>> caused by blockage of no stream.
>> Okay.
>> For the past 3 months, right?
>> Yeah. So, apostle before you prayed, I
had this headache which was as a result
of the symptoms of sinos. I remember in
the last miracle service, you had prayed
for blocked nose. So, I I had two
blocked nose. But during that miracle
service, one got okay, but the other one
was still blocked and um cozant that was
treating me gave me air drop which I was
using.
>> And right now, what happened to you?
Right now the headache that I had when I
came there which was completely gone has
gone. Yes.
>> In the name of Jesus for you and my
brother here I declare perfection for
you both by the power of Jesus. Can we
give Jesus a big hand clap? Yes sir.
>> All right. So Apostle our brother here
Ezekiel came all the way from Belsa.
>> You're welcome. Most welcome.
>> He came he's been having back pain for 6
months
>> now. Are you noticing what what's been
happening? You see, every time you see
recurrent miracles like this, I told you
that miracles when they are recurrent,
there's a message to it. God is just
using the bodily objects to speak a
message. Correcting uh bodies and all of
that, healing insanity and all of that.
Um we receive the miracles, but we must
learn to discern the message that come
with the miracles in the name of Jesus
Christ. Before the army became a strong
exceeding great army, the first miracle
was that bones were joined to bones.
Bones struck of structure. And there
cannot be order until there is
structure. Hallelujah. Praise the name
of the Lord. So I'm praying for you that
everything that is in disarray in your
life, your business, your destiny by the
power that raised Christ from the dead,
let there be a reordering right now.
>> You believe that? Shout amen.
>> Amen.
>> So sir, he said something very
interesting. He said he casually said
told God that God if you heal me I'll
come out.
>> You casually
No, no, I'm joking. Joking. Okay.
>> Yes, daddy. Cuz I'm a very shy person.
So I casually said it at the back. I
even have to just drag myself to
>> and right now
>> and and go ahead.
>> Perfected in Jesus name. Never returns
to you again. Perfection in Jesus name.
I've also my little friend here
>> wants to give this testimony himself.
>> Thank you sir.
>> How are you my friend?
>> I'm fine.
>> Go ahead. Oh my
>> my little friend. Don't cry. Huh? Don't
cry.
>> All right.
You people should celebrate God for this
child. Some of you
at his age, you were still idol
worshippers.
>> You are you are not even um so for a boy
like this to be this coherent and go
ahead my friend.
>> So last Friday night
I was I was playing with my toys and
then like I mistakenly um
left it free. Then I got like
you know the you know the type of
electrical pain. It just like got me
here on the tomb. And that night I had
to bear the pain from this to this and
till today that we should check
ourselves and
>> and you check
just a little close to God.
>> It's just a little close to God.
>> Yes.
In the name of Jesus Christ we pray.
That's that's the father.
>> So yes and apostle can you also just
quickly add something then okay apostle
this our little boy here is into
robotics
>> as small as so he was making you know
building.
>> Oh I get what he's saying. That's what
he was saying.
>> Yes. That he pricricked he was making a
Lego and then he pricricked his hands.
>> Ah okay.
>> An aeroplane. So he made
>> and that's the mother. Okay. Let her
finish it. Yes. Yes. So he was making a
Lego aeroplane. So when he puts it he
puts the even
>> How old is he?
>> He's seven.
>> Seven.
>> Yes. So it's it's new for me as well. So
he puts all the Arduino gadgets and he
starts to spin.
>> So he got injured.
>> So yes. So cuz he's spiky.
>> Okay.
>> Yes. So
>> and right now he's saying he's he's felt
a relief.
>> Yes.
>> Okay. In the name of Jesus, we decree
over this boy beyond the healing of his
hands. May God empower his mind.
Josiah was a king at age 9. Joash was a
king at age 8. We pray for this boy by
the power of the Holy Spirit. May he be
mighty on time
in Jesus name. And we use him to pray
for all our children here in the name of
Jesus Christ. Receive for your child by
the power of the Holy Spirit. Let them
be of quick understanding
of quick understanding in Jesus name.
God bless you my dear friend. God bless
you. Congratulations. All right.
>> Yes, please,
>> sir. Sir, we have a few more testimonies
here and we also have some online, but
our brother here is from Lagos.
>> From Lagos.
>> Okay.
>> Straight to the point, my friend.
>> My name is Mr. Christopher. I came from
Lagos. I arrive arrived Friday night.
So, when I came in, I was feeling this
severe fever. So, my friend that gave me
the apartment I was staying with got a
tablet for me. So, what I
>> If you're yet to submit your request,
please make sure you pass it very
quickly. We're about to pray over the
request. If there's anyone who is yet to
submit, just lift it, wave it, and then
the ushers will pick it. Would you move
it to the side? Just just pass it to
anybody at the aisle so that you make it
easy for the ushers. But make sure it's
lifted so that it's easy for them to
pick up. Yes, please.
>> So, apostle in in summary, he actually
came here feverish and when you were
praying, he actually connected, open up
his heart and now you're completely
perfected. I pray for you, my friend.
Not only will you go healed [music] in
the name of Jesus, we'll be wrapping up
by speaking a blessing and an
impartation. You would not need to tell
people you came here. The wisdom, the
grace, the favor of God will be so
deposited in your life in Jesus name.
God bless you and thank you for coming.
>> Yes, please. Next person.
>> Okay. Good evening sir.
>> How are you?
>> Fine sir. I've been having reoccurring
fever forever two weeks.
>> Okay.
>> I I've even treated it but it still came
back this afternoon before come to
service. I was very weak. I was even
cold. When I laid there, I covered
myself. I was not planning on live
streaming. Yes.
>> But I had to force myself that [music] I
must be here. And then while you were
praying, I was at the gallery. I
couldn't even stand. I just had to kneel
down, lay my hands on my head. And then
to the glory of God, I'm strong.
>> You're completely strong in Jesus name.
You remain perfected forever in Jesus
name. Can we have one or two more and
then that wraps it up so we can pray
over the requests?
>> Thank you. Um, daddy, sorry about that.
>> Yes.
>> So, um, she has a testimony from a
friend of hers,
>> okay,
>> whose mom has been sick.
>> Um, she said they took the mother to a
hospital. She has been disoriented and
unable to walk since Tuesday.
>> Okay.
>> So, they did a CT scan for her and they
said one of the things that they found
out was that the size of her brain has
shrunken um not as is it used to be
before.
>> Okay. So, but right now she encouraged
the friend to ensure that they connect
to service tonight. And while that was
going on and you were giving the
prophetic word, she asked them, she
asked the mother, that's the friend now
asked the mother to do what she couldn't
do before. And lo and behold, the mother
was able to stand up by herself. This
was something that she couldn't do since
Tuesday.
>> Amazing.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Where's the mom? Where's your mom?
>> She's in Lagos.
>> Yes, sir. in the name of Jesus. If she's
following mommy, we rejoice with your
testimony and we use your daughter as a
point of contact to speak perfection for
you in Jesus marvelous name. Amen.
Congratulations. Let's give her friend a
big God bless you. Can we take one or
two online very quickly? One or two.
Yes, please. Apostle, this is from
Cynthia Ini watching from South Africa.
>> Okay.
>> I lost my sense of smell in April after
a covid like flu. Apostle mentioned my
case. My sense of smell is restored. I
smell vicks now.
>> Are you celebrating?
>> Which I could not smell since April.
Thank God for allowing God to use you.
This is from Gloria. I have had this
lump in my breast for over a month now.
And it became bigger and more painful. I
had told God that I don't want to
service negativity with my money. But I
was having a rethink. I had planned to
check it out. But today I felt the pain
stop as apostle prophesied and the lump
has disappeared
>> in the name of Jesus.
>> I am still in shock. Before now I could
not touch that part of my breast. But
now I feel nothing to the glory of God.
Finally this is from Miss UA. I just got
my healing. I had had back pain for the
past 2 days. I could barely walk and it
came with a sharp pain. I got instantly
healed during this miracle service. I
have run, I have jumped, I have twisted
from side to side and it is amazing.
Jesus is Lord. I am online and
immediately apostles started worshiping.
I felt the power of God over me. And I
got healed. I mean instantly healed. I
am not trying to claim it by faith.
>> Amen.
>> Hallelujah.
>> For this and all the others, let's lift
our hands and thank him. Go ahead and
thank him. Let's act like grateful
people. We are a house that is very
intentional [music] about the doings of
God in our midst. Father, we thank you.
We bless you. Let the nations know you
as the doer and the worker of mighty and
strange things in the name of Jesus.
Now, whether you are seated or standing,
would you stretch your hands to these
requests? So, this is what I'm going to
do very quickly. I'm going to lay my
hands over
this request and speak over it. Once I'm
done speaking over it, I will make the
altar call and the prophetic
declarations. Once I do that, I'm going
to clear the way for the next 10 to 15
minutes. Um, your miracle, you're going
to come and stand here and pastor is
going to lead us through a time of
prophetic praise. is just going to blow
over you. Um, I'll tell you this first
and foremost personal. Thank you. Thank
you. This is a pleasant pleasant
surprise. Our revenge this one vengeance
God and me. Vengeance. Vengeance is us.
So everybody note it is 1 zero. Now um
it will soon be 1 one then 2 1 then 3 1
then 51 then 31 then 91. My own football
I don't score 45. If I score 100, 300,
500, praise the name of the Lord.
Hallelujah. Amen. [music] And we're
truly grateful. We honor you. We love
you. Thank you for this pleasant
surprise. Thank you. Thank you so much.
We receive of your ministry. And so,
we're going to have that time. For those
of you who are connected across the
globe, just know that we're still
blowing the trumpet. We're going to
blast that trumpet. We want every devil
to know that it's a new season. And how
many of you know that we're wrapping up
the first half of the year? So dance
your way, sing your way, jump your way,
prophesy your way into the second half
of the year [music] in the name of
Jesus. He said, "Though your beginning
be small, your latter end shall greatly
[music] increase." So let there be a
latter end dance, a rejoicing dance in
the name of Jesus. For now, let your
hands be stretched forth here and begin
to make declarations by the power of
God. We can never have enough of prayer.
He said we should always pray. [music]
We prayed last month. We prayed last
week. We're still praying. Father, in
the name of Jesus, turn captivities
around by the [music] power of the Holy
Ghost. Are you speaking? In the name of
Jesus, thank you for the ones you have
answered. I have brought new ones
because I believe you are still the same
yesterday, today, and forever. Someone
decree and declare by the power of the
Holy Spirit. Some of you are praying for
your loved ones. Some of you are [music]
declaring over yourself, your children,
your loved ones who are lost. Let's
pray. There is nothing you cannot do.
>> There's no mountain you cannot move.
If [music] you have said it, then you
will do it. [music]
You have a track record of keeping your
word
and you're not about [singing and music]
to stop doing.
You are [music] mighty.
>> You are mighty. [music]
>> [music]
[music]
>> In the name of Jesus, I bow my knees to
the father of our Lord Jesus Christ and
I speak over this request by faith. This
is an aggregate of the desires of God's
people from within us, among us here,
and the many who have submitted by faith
across the nations of the earth. Father,
you are called Abba. You are pata, our
source, our sustainer, our protector,
our foundation, our defender. The Bible
says the name of the Lord is a strong
tower. It says the righteous runth to it
and they are saved. Therefore, Lord,
because we know it is your good pleasure
to give us the kingdom. We declare by
the power of the Holy Spirit that every
request here represented, let it be
turned to a testimony.
Let it be turned to a harvest. Again,
let it be turned to a testimony. Let it
be turned to a harvest. One last time,
be turned to a harvest in the mighty
name of Jesus Christ.
Let the God who answers prayers visit
this request and visit you in your home,
visit you in your office, visit your
family in the name of Jesus. And like we
said here, these Egyptians you see today
in the name of Jesus, the son of the
living God, may you see them no more
forever.
No more forever.
Someone shout thank you Jesus. Again
shout thank you Jesus. Please everyone
be upstanding. Everyone if you are able
to be upstanding let me make the altar
call very quickly.
You need Jesus. Jesus is calling for
you. He wants to give you a new
beginning. Please lend me your attention
everyone. When he gathers us like this,
he also draws to us and um among us
people who need to make their ways right
with Jesus. What does it mean to come to
Jesus? It means that you understand and
you recognize that on your own you are
not able to make your life count. The
Bible says, "For he so loved you, he
gave his only begotten son that
whosoever, and that includes you, that
believes on him, you should not perish,
but life have life everlasting." And uh
you may have tried to live life your
way, done everything you've known to do,
but it's very clear right now that life
will not work on your terms. You need to
subscribe to the one who is the author
and the finisher of your faith. I want
to thank you for coming already. I'm
going to make um a count one to five.
And I want someone who is very serious
and very honest, who understood my
teaching, who has seen the power of God,
and is saying, "Apostle, I get you
clearly, I get you loud, and I'm ready
to make it right with Jesus." As I count
one to five, all of you who are in the
overflow outside, just run to the front
and there, stand ready to surrender your
hearts to Jesus, all the overflows down
to the basement. Please move to your
LEDs. And then for those who are here up
the base um the balcony and those who
are here, please make your way. And to
the many who are connected online,
please make sure you don't shut down. Um
it matters that you make it right with
Jesus. I'm counting now. Please be on
your way. God bless you. One coonia
celebrate them. We're part of their
salvation story. Let it be that you
encourage them as they were on their way
to the cross. Two,
still counting. If you're coming, rush
quickly.
This is your moment. This is your part
of the service. Three. Apostle. I'm not
sure if I'm saved. I consider myself a
nice person. Can I still come?
Absolutely. Make your way. I remember
making this decision before, but I'm not
sure if things are still all right. Can
I come to have the assurance of
salvation? Please come. Four. One more
count and I begin to pray. If you're
rushing, please join them. It matters
that you start and finish the prayer.
Some of you arrive when we are saying
amen.
[music] Hallelujah.
Amen. And amen. God bless you. Please
with your hands lifted. Lifted onto
Jesus. You don't have to kneel. Your
hands lifted. For those who are outside,
do same. Your hands lifted. All the
overflows. All our expressions viewing
centers around the world. Please would
you lift your hands also at the same
time? We're praying now. This is unto
Jesus. Say after me as loud and as clear
as you are able to say, Lord Jesus,
tonight, I have heard your word. I have
seen your power. I believe you are the
son of God. I believe you died for my
sin. I believe you rose again for my
justification. Right now, I believe that
you are my savior. You are my lord. You
are my king. I receive you into my heart
and I declare that from today I'm a
child of God. I go from glory to glory,
grace to grace. Amen. With your hands
still lifted, Father, thank you for
these ones representing the many unseen
faces across the globe who are praying
this prayer concurrently. I pray for you
by the authority of scripture that your
sins are forgiven and the grace to walk
in victory from tonight is released upon
you. you go from glory to glory and
grace to grace for it's in Jesus
maratchless and marvelous name we pray.
[music] Amen. Please look to my right.
That will be your left from where you
are standing. There are counselors who
are willing to have a word with you.
Pray a quick prayer with you. Thereafter
you'll be back to your seat. God bless
you. Let's keep clapping. Let's
celebrate them like we understand the
miracle that just happened. [music]
Amen. Praise the name of the Lord. Okay.
So, I'll speak over your life now very
quickly and then I'll allow you to just
come and celebrate Jesus. For those of
you who made this decision online,
there's a QR um link code. Please make
sure that you scan it and let's know
that you made Jesus Lord of your life.
There are counselors that have been
trained. They will follow up on you and
make sure you are established in
righteousness in Jesus name. Have you
been blessed tonight? Let me speak over
your life as we not only end this month,
but end the first half of 2026. It's
still our year of deliverance and
exemption. Still our year of receiving
marvelous things from the Lord. And he's
spoken great things concerning us in
Zion. And we want to enforce it
prophetically. And as I make
declarations, please receive it. By the
way, I did not take the time to
appreciate Reverend Yu Kila. God bless
you, sir. Was carried away by the
ministration. We thank you. Whilst the
service was on, he came in all the way
from Jos. We love you. We honor you. May
God bless you, sir, in Jesus name.
Hallelujah.
Let's lift our hands. With lifted hands,
we worship
you.
With lifted hands,
[music] we worship
you.
We bow before [singing]
We [music]
honor you. We lift. [singing]
We worship
you. [music]
>> May your week be blessed.
>> Are there still believers here? May your
week be blessed.
That means today is still blessed.
Tomorrow Monday blessed,
Tuesday blessed,
Wednesday blessed,
Thursday blessed,
Friday blessed,
Saturday blessed,
Sunday blessed,
blessed with victory, blessed with
favor, blessed with fearful results,
blessed with a manifestation of wisdom,
BLESSED WITH STRATEGIC CONNECTIONS,
Enjoy the ministry of helpers.
Enjoy speed this week. Enjoy restoration
this week. Let me say that again. Enjoy
speed this week. Enjoy restoration this
week. If it will favor you, may it
happen in a hurry.
If it's for your lifting, may it happen
in a hurry. If it's for your rising, may
it happen in a hurry. If it's FOR
SORROW, WE CANCEL IT before it arrives.
If it's for pain, WE CANCEL IT BEFORE it
arrives. I call you the blessed of the
Lord. Let honor work in your life this
week. No man will despise [music] you.
Everyone connected to you is blessed for
your sake. Blessed are you in your going
out and your coming in the name of
Jesus. I declare over your prayer life
fresh fire.
Over your word study life fresh fire.
May your love for Jesus works hotter and
hotter. Next week you'll be in a hurry
to come here to testify.
May you see the goodness of God this
week as you step into July. I decree and
declare January to June together. May it
happen in your first week in July.
I prayed over a receiver JANUARY TO
JUNE. EVERY good thing that happened
aggregated, may it repeat itself in the
first week of July
in the name of Jesus Christ. May this be
the week where prophecy finds
expression.
May this be the week where your prayers
become manifest.
May this be the week where you lay hold
onto your testimonies
in the name of Jesus I pray. Shout seven
amens. Let's go.
5 6
7.
[music]
So we share the grace and you run. You
have everything to jump your
handkerchief whatever. Let's just allow
pastor Nat honor to have him here.
Ushher us prophetically
into an extraordinary July together.
Let's share the grace. The grace of our
Lord Jesus Christ, the love of God, the
sweet fellowship of the Holy Spirit rest
and abide with us now and forever more.
Amen. Surely
>> all the days of our lives as we dwell in
the house of the Lord forever and ever.
Amen. Ladies and gentlemen, Pastor
Nathaniel Bass.
>> Somebody shout hallelujah.
>> Isaiah 55:12. [music]
Isaiah 55:12. It says, "You shall go out
with joy."
How are you leaving June to July? Tell
with joy.
Are you ready?
For ye shall go out with joy. Somebody
release some joy.
[music]
Praise the Lord. [music] Praise the
Lord.
[music]
I said, "Praise the Lord.
Gallery, will you praise the [music]
Lord?
Gallery too,
will you praise the Lord, [music]
brothers? Praise the Lord. [music]
I said, "Praise the Lord." Praise the
Lord. Say, "Praise [music]
the Lord."
>> Praise the Lord. [music]
Say, "Praise the Lord."
Praise [music]
everybody.
Praise the Lord.
I [music] said, "Praise the Lord. Praise
the Lord. Praise the Lord. Praise the
Lord. [music] Praise the Lord.
Praise the Lord. Praise the [music]
Lord. Praise the Lord.
Praise his [music] name.
Praise the Lord. I said, "Have you
[music] have you had
you? Have you heard? Have you seen?
[music]
Have you seen? Have you heard? Have you
hear? Have you heard?
>> [music]
>> Have you seen
Have you heard what the Lord has done?
He has destroyed the world.
He has given [music] us the glory.
Savior.
Have you heard what
he [music] has?
He has given us victory.
That's why we [music] see
[music]
Say
Jesus higher.
[music]
Lifting Jesus higher.
Lifting [music] Jesus higher.
[music]
Higher.
Somebody shout hallelujah.
[music]
We call you everybody.
Let's go.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Hey, [music]
we call you everybody. [music]
Everybody,
[music] let's go.
[music]
Somebody raise your hand at him.
Somebody shout hallelujah. [music]
Say
[music]
here I come.
Say second half.
Here we come
on your [music] mind. Let go.
>> [music]
[music]
>> I [music] see some people just looking
around.
I have a word for them.
[music] I have a word for them.
Give me chance. I want to praise my
[music]
I want to [music] worship my God.
Hallelujah.
[music]
Hallelujah. [music]
I've come to celebrate. I've come to
celebrate. I've come to celebrate. I've
come to celebrate.
I've come to [music]
now.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Somebody say, [music]
"Are [music] you ready?
Children of the world,
[music]
ready to s
Children of
[music]
children of God,
ready to
[music]
children of God, will you shout
hallelujah? Shout hallelujah [music]
to God 10 times.
>> [music]
>> Jesus [music] there.
>> He
is there.
He
>> Somebody shout hallelujah.
[music]
I'm praising the valley.
Praise in the mountain.
Praise when [music] I'm sure.
Praise when I'm
praise when I'm
praise.
[music]
Are you ready?
Heat.
[music]
Heat. [music]
Heat. Heat.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Heat.
[music]
Heat.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Now I'm about to blow the trumpet over
you.
[music] Put that scripture for me.
Isaiah 55:2.
As you march out of June, [music]
Isaiah 55:12.
Somebody say mama. Somebody [music] say
mama. Somebody say mama. Somebody say
somebody [music] say somebody say
somebody say
my Jesus.
[music]
My Jesus.
>> [music]
>> Jesus
[music] Jesus
for you shall go [music] out with joy
and you'll be left with peace [music]
as you enter into July. The mountains
and the hills shall break forth before
you.
They will give you a standing ovation.
[music]
And all the trees of the field shall
clap their hands for you. [music]
Can I announce your
triumphant [music]
entry to the second house
with the sound of the trumpet? [music]
When we hear the sound of the trumpet,
you will shout a shout of celebration.
You shall be celebrated. Oh, [music]
[music]
heat.
Heat. [music]
[music]
Heat.
Heat. Heat.
[music]
>> [music]
>> He's a son of a [music]
[music]
>> [music]
>> Let it feel your second house. Let it
feel your life. Let it feel your
families. Let it feel Nigeria. [music]
Let it feel your lineage. Let it feel.
[music]
One more for the road.
E flat. One more [music] on the road.
Now find a partner.
In the second half, you will sing this
song.
The Lord has done it. [music]
The Lord has done it.
[music]
>> [music]
>> It has
[music]
it is
in the name of Jesus Christ. [music]
[music]
That's my story.
Heat. Heat.
[music]
Heat.
>> [music]
>> Heat. Heat. [music]
>> Apostle B, I think people like you. When
did they start liking me? Can I tell you
this? When God is silent, learn to hear
the voice [music] of silence. I'm
praying tonight. Everything you have
been carrying, this is the month [music]
to give birth to it.
Your weak beginning will experience
dimensions of favor [music] you have
never experienced.